[
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ka",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "か"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5c363fac-97f7-4324-aa78-ec6e7326c302"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ki",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "き"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0c76fbb2-d54c-4cf2-89b8-8e206c40970c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ku",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "く"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3c67a155-d837-4c1a-b1c2-822ca53f33b5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ke",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "け"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ddda98c2-cd92-4f68-aa27-cb48ca44eb03"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ko",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "こ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "38c743e6-a691-4a8a-a95d-27de0bbe6186"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "か",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "ka"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f5affcfc-41b7-4474-8fcc-4d770c5a71c3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "き",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "ki"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5480c222-f01e-4b7e-91b8-3c9f2a6a553e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "く",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "ku"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8c0c5b76-7706-4ae1-8d1b-0550ea8e2f49"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "け",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "ke"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9a14e36e-9c9e-43f0-add9-a3c452d72b3e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "こ",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "ko"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e2b5b818-9f7d-44e2-9d65-4cdfc84dec5e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "か",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "か"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "61f35cc2-be63-4161-893f-bf51b0def84b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "き",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "き"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d17da600-bbed-45e4-8096-90590c9c60b9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "く",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "く"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a523bd6f-c2a5-4b5c-aa35-49ecc9fe09b1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "け",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "け"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a781f680-62f9-4db6-8a78-ac5f41928ec4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "こ",
        "options": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
        "question": "こ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f3a00c17-41a9-411e-b476-602faa77ef8a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "か",
            "rightSide": "ka"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "き",
            "rightSide": "ki"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "く",
            "rightSide": "ku"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "け",
            "rightSide": "ke"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "こ",
            "rightSide": "ko"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "か",
            "rightSide": "ka"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "き",
            "rightSide": "ki"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "く",
            "rightSide": "ku"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "け",
            "rightSide": "ke"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "こ",
            "rightSide": "ko"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b82c1553-4c33-427c-bfea-7c14907332ef"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ka",
            "rightSide": "か"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ki",
            "rightSide": "き"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ku",
            "rightSide": "く"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ke",
            "rightSide": "け"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ko",
            "rightSide": "こ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ka",
            "rightSide": "か"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ki",
            "rightSide": "き"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ku",
            "rightSide": "く"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ke",
            "rightSide": "け"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ko",
            "rightSide": "こ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ec2c9a22-ef6a-4be0-bfd5-690e6584f92c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "16ef68e8-6b31-4c4a-8282-964b4973ed83"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "こい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "291338f5-be2d-4289-a6a7-017e93c4fb38"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1d0ed86b-94df-4de6-98af-4c0155c7b822"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いけ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2f495564-96f8-4e69-a434-f7de45c4febb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あか",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4a009a0e-c7f2-4049-b3ad-116947faab44"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おか",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "77e091c5-ca3a-4f9d-b8b1-e4487f5e1ea5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ta",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "た"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "24b5d535-8fd6-4c9e-ac32-417beb554fc0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "こいけい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "71def0b9-4e2a-4926-90d8-155dc25b2bdb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かお",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8b1c845d-ba45-4762-b3bd-fd6c4c7ef26d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きいろい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ろ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "64a281c6-71c8-4aee-8a00-d38cda520e04"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "うき",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["か", "き", "く", "け", "こ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "01736cf2-7b76-4fe8-88a1-a1f0f3d88fd6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "chi",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "ち"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "90872e59-e057-4419-bcf9-5aa76819f112"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "tsu",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "つ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8a529a48-1a7e-4d97-9b92-4df517ed3cbb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "te",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "て"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2e16bf0f-8ec3-424b-ba26-e3eab8c35b60"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "to",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "と"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d8474da4-6e28-4aa7-b590-c4c10dbfae8d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "た",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "ta"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e655b308-c504-4843-861b-9f7234ffcc4a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ち",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "chi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "352aa79a-91e0-4ec4-9297-c57f297a2620"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "つ",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "tsu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8fb081d8-64a3-446e-90ad-947ffbcb8986"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "て",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "te"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ee94c0d8-aa5a-4223-8030-47e00c42108c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "と",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "to"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a1501cfb-3709-40a1-af9c-3c3552270c3c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "た",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "た"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1cf228f7-4329-4524-9a72-091ec218c738"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ち",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "ち"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "69c7c740-fd2f-45aa-8c63-77e2f7d30568"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "つ",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "つ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "749a9e93-d3f4-4709-a7de-ab16421ad640"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "て",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "て"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bf7dbad1-15b5-433a-9c67-bf4ec22b14f6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "と",
        "options": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
        "question": "と"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6da93ccd-2905-4b25-8599-34c1601e49f9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "た",
            "rightSide": "ta"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ち",
            "rightSide": "chi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "つ",
            "rightSide": "tsu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "て",
            "rightSide": "te"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "と",
            "rightSide": "to"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "た",
            "rightSide": "ta"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ち",
            "rightSide": "chi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "つ",
            "rightSide": "tsu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "て",
            "rightSide": "te"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "と",
            "rightSide": "to"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b956431e-fbd8-4aeb-91f0-e6b6a89913d8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ta",
            "rightSide": "た"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "chi",
            "rightSide": "ち"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "tsu",
            "rightSide": "つ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "te",
            "rightSide": "て"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "to",
            "rightSide": "と"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ta",
            "rightSide": "た"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "chi",
            "rightSide": "ち"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "tsu",
            "rightSide": "つ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "te",
            "rightSide": "て"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "to",
            "rightSide": "と"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c724425b-0f05-4e92-8bce-468fb2143849"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "たこ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "た",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9311d04c-9bb9-4e0d-bf43-8ba440105c0b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちか",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "99a44128-7edb-4270-94fa-9529f457bcc8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "つき",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "つ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8d518a12-fea8-40f6-88b8-36211b801b00"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "sa",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "さ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "387129dd-08b9-400d-83c3-a0498e2ade9a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "shi",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "し"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "90f584dc-9e08-4703-b55b-180178801b1a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "su",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "す"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dddd6943-8068-41f3-a94b-d47bd801635a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "se",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "せ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "11974e08-98cb-49f1-8e03-69d1f05711bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "so",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "そ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "46751b9d-c98f-4f28-ada8-e50faa2cb153"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "さ",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "sa"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6cffb2ac-3f23-4900-b47f-748396adddf6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "し",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "shi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bb981335-34af-48f9-a5fc-7c6acc4af8bf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "す",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "su"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "733dd5cd-83ac-46cc-b115-6bc48112398f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "せ",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "se"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "79e4fa42-fdc6-4638-9e2e-b9dc3f0c4834"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "そ",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "so"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c7e8ba0f-27b7-42d8-8943-a42ffb8f43ab"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "さ",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "さ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d6ac5812-fb16-412f-8e6a-74fea9e41eb1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "し",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "し"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b0052baa-9f8a-49fd-87f8-f056378dfa85"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "す",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "す"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "56a8db6b-ed2e-4463-9b07-463f22fc2a2a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "せ",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "せ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9bbf9d31-f5f5-420d-bd88-a79b4fab5856"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "そ",
        "options": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
        "question": "そ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f90be9af-d465-4c84-84e3-eff7bf52e7c5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "てき",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "て",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c9e0a3fd-7468-4295-b9dc-aea7e90a1ce6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あと",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6c04b814-bf51-4b50-87aa-59381da0ff9d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "え",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "え"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c10fb6e4-4021-4602-b8cd-8dd3666b13b7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "お",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "お"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a39108da-6161-4edb-ad0a-434ca9b58130"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "あ",
            "rightSide": "a"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "い",
            "rightSide": "i"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "う",
            "rightSide": "u"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "え",
            "rightSide": "e"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "お",
            "rightSide": "o"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "あ",
            "rightSide": "a"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "い",
            "rightSide": "i"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "う",
            "rightSide": "u"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "え",
            "rightSide": "e"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "お",
            "rightSide": "o"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "07a38259-95b8-495c-b911-292993228597"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "a",
            "rightSide": "あ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "i",
            "rightSide": "い"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "u",
            "rightSide": "う"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "e",
            "rightSide": "え"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "o",
            "rightSide": "お"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "a",
            "rightSide": "あ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "i",
            "rightSide": "い"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "u",
            "rightSide": "う"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "e",
            "rightSide": "え"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "o",
            "rightSide": "お"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "965bf64e-d222-4a41-a42a-2e87e4806c46"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あおい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8a7af883-d725-4f42-9283-27a822066e7b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いえ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1ac2ea97-8151-4ac8-8d1c-68002d08894e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "99195edf-f59b-4d78-954e-2278965e6c3a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "さ",
            "rightSide": "sa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "し",
            "rightSide": "shi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "す",
            "rightSide": "su"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "せ",
            "rightSide": "se"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "そ",
            "rightSide": "so"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "さ",
            "rightSide": "sa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "し",
            "rightSide": "shi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "す",
            "rightSide": "su"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "せ",
            "rightSide": "se"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "そ",
            "rightSide": "so"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2840cfa6-fcc7-49df-bc81-8e6fbe1cc6b5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "sa",
            "rightSide": "さ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "shi",
            "rightSide": "し"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "su",
            "rightSide": "す"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "se",
            "rightSide": "せ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "so",
            "rightSide": "そ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "sa",
            "rightSide": "さ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "shi",
            "rightSide": "し"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "su",
            "rightSide": "す"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "se",
            "rightSide": "せ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "so",
            "rightSide": "そ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4b58c07c-5041-427d-be73-0d9a788c9222"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "さけ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3a0b74b1-1e1a-4fbd-a3e5-6771ca6587bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "すし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "す",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "865491cf-4b8c-4b22-ab72-f7d696e912bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しお",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dd8e0b2b-f6c1-4672-a54a-a355a84ff96a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c30a6fce-550d-4305-a32e-4080a82d0318"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かさ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7f3523d9-e752-4392-ba01-aa4fe2890ab9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "せき",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "せ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cefd23c9-fa1f-4e3f-a326-1fcb0dc29497"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "けしき",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2e2a5bce-3299-4e56-95d2-d142efd57946"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いさかい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "52cf3767-2dd4-4256-8d04-74f1c324a913"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "a",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "あ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8240db46-5037-4fca-8f53-20122971da36"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "i",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "い"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1fe8dfcb-be86-442c-84cb-bd0177835d1d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "u",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "う"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "77086a9e-8ee2-4743-8deb-1c2bf53f8792"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "e",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "え"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "82261a20-1fc3-4812-a7d6-8c3ee8993440"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "o",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "お"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "189d29f9-d338-456e-9109-b8e6ae0720c5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あ",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "a"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b9230ee2-800b-409b-a520-ea23f36c765e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "い",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "i"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ad5747b3-3f7e-4586-9388-91461e86c4f6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "う",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "u"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9d154b17-bceb-4411-b750-975cd6cefc5b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "え",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "e"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9b5c4062-07fd-4072-aaa0-8bd5115e9537"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "お",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "o"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a97c64f1-1cf5-422d-9d68-5260ee81666a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あ",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "あ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "34855e76-6c19-43ed-b774-df30bba7cc66"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "い",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "い"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "328ee1e9-b285-4357-9d9e-f9e5e98842f9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "う",
        "options": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
        "question": "う"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9bde39f1-913c-4345-bd99-6434211d2674"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あお",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6cf59fef-8a21-49f7-a771-d8d1abecdb30"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あえ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b37465e6-8ef8-435b-bcb8-144e496f890d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "うえ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5861602b-a954-448a-9758-75a1e1f2a4b4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "85646c77-b45a-4803-be31-99cdc6eb22ed"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いお",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a067c388-f22b-4eb9-838e-0b87ed58f5ec"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あうえ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b7b54b24-e83b-479e-813c-3914902ecb18"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おいお",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["あ", "い", "う", "え", "お"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ba858a0b-3fc1-4e16-9b61-ffa2f50295ca"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あさけ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8a3d99b5-a83b-4f70-aa8a-baa957e46453"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かしこい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["さ", "し", "す", "せ", "そ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "470e1876-5677-4da0-8c13-a18fb49466f6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "こと",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8cd27f2f-206f-4edb-a721-9e5a3e2dc1cb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いと",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "803ec7c8-8341-432b-9899-000e93cb3c06"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "とけい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "07cafb76-3e56-4b15-9599-ee366e7653fa"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かたち",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "た",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c8dba447-6c89-4143-8196-c34c58b39192"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "さとい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["た", "ち", "つ", "て", "と"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d7890b0a-0557-474a-8b56-66a8578ceadc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "na",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "な"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a3eb1733-a0ef-419f-a61a-e464542eb6e4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ni",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "に"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3b31e234-3fb0-4f3a-b5dd-8adb9d19d54a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "nu",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "ぬ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "54100ab5-1a19-4ac4-8760-5601c66a5a3d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ne",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "ね"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "60789f18-c6da-49ea-85f9-17c0a510a4b5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "no",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "の"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e59ca5eb-4a7a-4085-ade5-12873d84cab1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "な",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "na"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "62fda429-08fb-4962-b284-b114dd82739e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "に",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "ni"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "866e1eea-b157-435f-a44b-998199d00ccb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぬ",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "nu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c632e2a8-982f-4a8d-9f20-7135325e5afe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ね",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "ne"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6443768b-5b8e-44c5-887e-27f5ee431246"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "の",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "no"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "94d2c3c7-11e1-425e-af29-4806fb581b00"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "な",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "な"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cf382e26-8183-413b-ae4a-d1a1b813c9a0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "に",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "に"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "418d57e8-faa4-4eec-a352-0dd1b9520dde"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぬ",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "ぬ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e3d44526-9f5c-42ed-99ad-b04a3c0af27b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ね",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "ね"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "211a2636-a223-49b2-9997-3a552e410099"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "の",
        "options": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
        "question": "の"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d691047b-381f-4d7f-813b-00ea779acb99"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "な",
            "rightSide": "na"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "に",
            "rightSide": "ni"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぬ",
            "rightSide": "nu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ね",
            "rightSide": "ne"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "の",
            "rightSide": "no"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "な",
            "rightSide": "na"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "に",
            "rightSide": "ni"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぬ",
            "rightSide": "nu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ね",
            "rightSide": "ne"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "の",
            "rightSide": "no"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "46652af8-ee40-48e9-9ecf-e6c33fe8623b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "na",
            "rightSide": "な"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ni",
            "rightSide": "に"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nu",
            "rightSide": "ぬ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ne",
            "rightSide": "ね"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "no",
            "rightSide": "の"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "na",
            "rightSide": "な"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ni",
            "rightSide": "に"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nu",
            "rightSide": "ぬ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ne",
            "rightSide": "ね"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "no",
            "rightSide": "の"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "eaa7ad97-56c5-4639-9b71-49637626d1e7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "なに",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "な",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "75d1bfe7-613f-46e8-9a50-de70d198a46c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "のこす",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "の",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "す",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e94f4f57-d8a5-4e5c-999a-d74a904d14d5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぬの",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぬ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "の",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d7955cd1-597a-498a-96ad-5218ab818290"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ねこ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ね",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "56d99051-a78d-4989-887d-f23f24c06196"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "のち",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "の",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fa5b5bf4-5e0c-42ff-9d39-90388672fbbe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あさの",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "の",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a3f3b3e2-83de-4410-825d-1e2555592fe1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "503e2537-7251-48f8-9f64-3569013e9bcf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ことの",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "の",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d39b1d06-23a7-4ac6-b5ac-75399427c8a1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "たに",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "た",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "01a6e9ed-dc02-4a2e-8fc7-3001fab173b5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いぬ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ぬ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね", "の"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8ca075fb-eda6-4bd3-91cb-0c6f49a7593c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ha",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "は"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "09352ab8-a482-49c8-b80b-d2e887418918"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "hi",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "ひ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "14810fb3-23e4-4cde-bd1d-26678f020e9e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "fu",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "ふ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e83c4174-2919-4ce7-90bc-59d63c2edc34"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "he",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "へ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fa712e4a-070f-4d0a-b8cb-f7a26a4ead1e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ho",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "ほ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ea2828e6-9d4f-4222-bb83-f7d680e89b72"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ん",
        "options": ["ん"],
        "question": "ん"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ん"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4053bfa1-110d-48fc-b7c9-bc5e288343dc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "は",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "ha"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "72c8064f-5a8e-4e9c-951f-63139f8457bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひ",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "hi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f8290cea-447f-4539-a2c6-bfcee75638a5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ふ",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "fu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c70dc3e3-c652-455e-aa46-5aab01031630"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "へ",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "he"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9d85b47a-ed4f-4241-bb79-e1b10bbe2c02"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ほ",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "ho"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3be16353-be9e-45f9-8295-25cc007ee757"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "は",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "は"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0728135a-e030-436c-afab-0cdb8b5cfe0e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひ",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "ひ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "59fad013-421f-4d52-ade0-bef4ce6ce3ba"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ふ",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "ふ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2592b35e-58d3-4a0c-9f4b-d63ffff0586a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "へ",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "へ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0bb674d9-d0de-41c8-b814-f36735dfeb10"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ほ",
        "options": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
        "question": "ほ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8f6af1c2-e880-423f-aa72-1519ad423ce5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "は",
            "rightSide": "ha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ひ",
            "rightSide": "hi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ふ",
            "rightSide": "fu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "へ",
            "rightSide": "he"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ほ",
            "rightSide": "ho"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "は",
            "rightSide": "ha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ひ",
            "rightSide": "hi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ふ",
            "rightSide": "fu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "へ",
            "rightSide": "he"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ほ",
            "rightSide": "ho"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "64151a0c-5a13-4aa2-b2fb-3b4d58c457af"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ha",
            "rightSide": "は"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hi",
            "rightSide": "ひ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "fu",
            "rightSide": "ふ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "he",
            "rightSide": "へ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ho",
            "rightSide": "ほ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ha",
            "rightSide": "は"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hi",
            "rightSide": "ひ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "fu",
            "rightSide": "ふ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "he",
            "rightSide": "へ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ho",
            "rightSide": "ほ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5cb69e6d-5763-4966-8d08-326044791898"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "はこ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "は",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c99717c3-a5aa-4e99-a1b3-d5b3a250d0b4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひと",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ひ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "af18d241-7a63-4dc0-a04f-89a564617ed0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ふね",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ふ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ね",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a39880cd-969a-4b81-b644-389cd589c3fc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "へた",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "へ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "た",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "88a85607-d7f9-4c50-ba9b-53a91f5108b4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ほし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ほ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6241230f-67e9-45b9-9b0f-ac3285610b36"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "はな",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "は",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "な",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "242f3941-529c-4530-9db7-90e8c0b7f8a3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ほね",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ほ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ね",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "212999e9-1692-4d4a-9fb0-0cf78c581cb5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ふく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ふ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bce4c3bf-e9ea-4203-845b-7fb114417fe2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "はし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "は",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9731ed13-58f9-4909-bb8b-82f1ba2c20d7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひかり",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ひ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "り",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ", "ほ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8e92a224-6f0c-4546-8b4c-056baad76d5c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ma",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "ま"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "33818ef1-be25-4f9b-aa88-5647f9f8cfee"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "mi",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "み"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d9439f4c-caae-452f-9467-c92aef0f71ba"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "mu",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "む"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "41fe989f-8fe0-4072-94d0-b699048eb970"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "me",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "め"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b357f2d7-98fa-48ee-ac5d-731421178b6e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "mo",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "も"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "88589c8b-ab9b-4fcb-8b39-9f9ba264e7b2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ま",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "ma"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0c2feef9-1895-425f-ba73-f2f889a4b604"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "み",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "mi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d850223b-32ca-4e5b-aa8d-ba61d7b79d04"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "む",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "mu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ef8dfd81-ed24-4a34-9c67-602c2248bc32"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "め",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "me"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f117eeca-27ed-434f-b9b7-aa3c66818d09"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "も",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "mo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ebb901ae-d5d2-42b6-934f-8cb4cb15d98a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ま",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "ま"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "95713d95-b126-4280-9d6f-8b3e3cb4937d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "み",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "み"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b1497d02-780c-4971-8f98-091f7437d8cd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "む",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "む"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "de3df2b8-52ed-4f36-b473-54e5fe1acecc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "め",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "め"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e987924f-edf3-44b6-b223-e512ef943e05"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "も",
        "options": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
        "question": "も"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6d78be39-4671-4cde-9424-cf81d3b277f2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ま",
            "rightSide": "ma"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "み",
            "rightSide": "mi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "む",
            "rightSide": "mu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "め",
            "rightSide": "me"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "も",
            "rightSide": "mo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ま",
            "rightSide": "ma"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "み",
            "rightSide": "mi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "む",
            "rightSide": "mu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "め",
            "rightSide": "me"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "も",
            "rightSide": "mo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "046bb4e1-7cf6-44c6-8160-df4d27c74593"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ma",
            "rightSide": "ま"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mi",
            "rightSide": "み"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mu",
            "rightSide": "む"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "me",
            "rightSide": "め"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mo",
            "rightSide": "も"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ma",
            "rightSide": "ま"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mi",
            "rightSide": "み"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mu",
            "rightSide": "む"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "me",
            "rightSide": "め"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mo",
            "rightSide": "も"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "89c5338e-216b-4efa-ab73-4c87ed3273f8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "まち",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ま",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f1611bc7-0576-44cd-b4bd-ad67ac1acc86"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みみ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a4692907-fe2e-4855-a538-2b661704ce75"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "むし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "む",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9364058c-1f10-483f-bc6f-35d6a7e30c7d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "めし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "め",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8fcc4526-e2f1-4ce6-aef1-d5161f466e9b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "もも",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "も",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "も",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a1332588-bbe8-4004-bfad-8b3f0f04e212"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "はなみ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "は",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "な",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cef1aa6e-946b-4566-b438-e0bcb9a7e031"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "さむい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "む",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "16b07960-108e-4479-9d67-1266dc429f4b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひま",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ひ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ま",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "55d1c2a9-0506-42bd-b140-e64d6682f077"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "とも",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "も",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f9a982f9-893b-4137-978a-dda4f5c3ab8f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "うみ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ま", "み", "む", "め", "も"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2f7e923e-d347-432a-ab48-197ef6cdb00e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ya",
        "options": ["ya", "yu", "yo"],
        "question": "や"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bf80b3ac-8077-47b0-b96e-5a7cfd3c321d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "yu",
        "options": ["ya", "yu", "yo"],
        "question": "ゆ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e1e4045c-c9fb-4c3f-88f0-210a65c2ad2f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "yo",
        "options": ["ya", "yu", "yo"],
        "question": "よ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "561f984d-20d1-4af3-a3ed-1d9648bdd8ed"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "や",
        "options": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
        "question": "ya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a1e75b68-88ae-4ba0-95da-c6c989ad6228"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゆ",
        "options": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
        "question": "yu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0869c2ea-34aa-45fe-921a-b44c24eec528"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "よ",
        "options": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
        "question": "yo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b9051614-b128-4a46-ad01-f1f16ab6f8ca"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "や",
        "options": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
        "question": "や"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e28c6105-8148-4c17-bed9-01a781704401"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゆ",
        "options": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
        "question": "ゆ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "832873ae-aa6e-4dde-943e-e78c83598a3b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "よ",
        "options": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
        "question": "よ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "357408b9-44c2-4b09-bc62-4ea97bf33eac"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "や",
            "rightSide": "ya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゆ",
            "rightSide": "yu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "よ",
            "rightSide": "yo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "や",
            "rightSide": "ya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゆ",
            "rightSide": "yu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "よ",
            "rightSide": "yo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c9773344-239a-4bc3-8ff9-b749c3a7231b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ya",
            "rightSide": "や"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "yu",
            "rightSide": "ゆ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "yo",
            "rightSide": "よ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ya",
            "rightSide": "や"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "yu",
            "rightSide": "ゆ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "yo",
            "rightSide": "よ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f3b5057c-e371-4d3d-9902-ecac08fe56c5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "やま",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "や",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ま",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "21aaad62-8bd0-463a-b312-3c45e0f79e0a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゆき",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ゆ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "811a011f-b986-4465-8d6f-017d22aefab6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "よる",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "よ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "る",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "97c9221d-225f-4a43-a329-1ce1a98e88ac"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "やさしい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "や",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "526d4095-2621-46d4-bdb6-9fe7c0f10dfb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゆめ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ゆ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "め",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e7758ac9-4676-4023-9e15-7359932aac73"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "やすみ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "や",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "す",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3c8009e3-5f02-4c23-a94d-e6fb31087dbd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "よこ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "よ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5b5cc581-89dd-46f3-935b-13935bafe78d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゆび",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ゆ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "び",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cf5a51ab-d74b-4ed7-95d0-4efb7b35651b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "やね",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "や",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ね",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d72ab344-c5f0-4924-9dab-fb3a49cda80c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "よてい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "よ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "て",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["や", "ゆ", "よ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "489f558b-dccc-41ad-b891-6d8e8c0dabb9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ra",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "ら"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2e46a5f7-ac2b-4d94-ba1e-42107a47258e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ri",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "り"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "21d0026d-2e74-4ef3-8bc8-572878ca141a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ru",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "る"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fc4095bc-b4f5-48ea-a211-0baf0cfc6fe5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "re",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "れ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f47949cd-bafc-4906-891c-21252bec6f4f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ro",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "ろ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f6f3ea0a-2404-460b-920d-d6f963082165"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ら",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "ra"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f0d93428-a4f0-4be1-86f0-c65e2413fb6c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "り",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "ri"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9e924d36-594b-4673-b26c-175698aff0d6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "る",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "ru"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "32534d80-f3a9-4185-9cea-ca412ec79780"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "れ",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "re"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b097cbaf-bbc2-4c2a-8e1d-8244d7a6344c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ろ",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "ro"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bb65ba03-52d5-4198-ad35-bacc755c7945"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ら",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "ら"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a3595f5d-d23f-4c98-9a2a-86d83de54474"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "り",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "り"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "59a41af3-44c8-43e6-a543-f785df2fcf7a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "る",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "る"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1d937b4c-c4a4-4067-82fd-c2ae0ff833d3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "れ",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "れ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cb919922-0bbd-4cfd-8bfd-d8102f8c33da"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ろ",
        "options": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
        "question": "ろ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "17cab2fc-51e0-485e-adad-d62082ce9df1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ら",
            "rightSide": "ra"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "り",
            "rightSide": "ri"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "る",
            "rightSide": "ru"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "れ",
            "rightSide": "re"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ろ",
            "rightSide": "ro"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ら",
            "rightSide": "ra"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "り",
            "rightSide": "ri"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "る",
            "rightSide": "ru"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "れ",
            "rightSide": "re"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ろ",
            "rightSide": "ro"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "86f373c3-a051-4bfe-b1c2-198b68e5c2aa"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ra",
            "rightSide": "ら"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ri",
            "rightSide": "り"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ru",
            "rightSide": "る"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "re",
            "rightSide": "れ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ro",
            "rightSide": "ろ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ra",
            "rightSide": "ら"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ri",
            "rightSide": "り"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ru",
            "rightSide": "る"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "re",
            "rightSide": "れ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ro",
            "rightSide": "ろ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "69bb8711-6d20-49f7-a678-80d91446639c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "らいおん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ら",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "51056023-e74e-419b-8cc3-7cde88ca379a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りす",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "り",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "す",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "92ebaa91-f036-4746-b83a-1de71b9bc210"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "るす",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "る",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "す",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2499d561-08ff-4123-a281-452857aa73a0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "れきし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "れ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c01429eb-72aa-49b8-9905-ddae451154a1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ろうか",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ろ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7cf4b698-e712-451f-a07a-56d5100bb2c5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "そら",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "そ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ら",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cbceb190-1e65-420f-b3bf-ff63cde38611"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "からて",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ら",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "て",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6eda39b6-8c8b-43e4-9739-1025b86c8231"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "はら",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "は",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ら",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dcb17e5b-c246-4ce6-be90-da5407061bbd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みらい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ら",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "39c524a6-e7c8-482c-bbc7-9205ab6e5e29"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゆれる",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ゆ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "れ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "る",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ら", "り", "る", "れ", "ろ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7e1b670b-79cc-4495-bf62-167c78f8f2e5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "wa",
        "options": ["wa", "wo"],
        "question": "わ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ba98429f-f43a-43d8-b9a0-e82baf4baa21"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "wo",
        "options": ["wa", "wo"],
        "question": "を"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9d40f5bd-888c-4ccd-986c-fe00f8771972"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "わ",
        "options": ["わ", "を"],
        "question": "wa"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "29c7ebbc-90cb-4f73-9b6d-1703b8ee4378"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "を",
        "options": ["わ", "を"],
        "question": "wo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "01b7ecd3-0a35-4394-b579-703c943c6f8b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "わ",
        "options": ["わ", "を"],
        "question": "わ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d8775d9e-7e8d-4a01-b229-f0e1a7388fb8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "を",
        "options": ["わ", "を"],
        "question": "を"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "27cae880-d4f5-40d0-a8f4-c64099ab8400"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "わ",
            "rightSide": "wa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "を",
            "rightSide": "wo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "わ",
            "rightSide": "wa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "を",
            "rightSide": "wo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8e124db8-03b3-4b59-b15b-648fe4ab365f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "wa",
            "rightSide": "わ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "wo",
            "rightSide": "を"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "wa",
            "rightSide": "わ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "wo",
            "rightSide": "を"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "eadb8a23-0104-4760-9805-649663722585"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "わに",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8aef2cdf-03e3-43af-9380-4ecb9d4acfe0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "わたし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "た",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "078c5d65-6ed8-421b-9a8e-90bcdade74b3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "わらう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ら",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1f576b31-9f7e-4f40-acc9-180fce4edfd3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "われる",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "れ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "る",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "730f309b-617c-4be2-8aab-60f635963aca"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "わかめ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "め",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "84c20bdd-6bf8-4c90-9015-0d481354ce09"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きをわるくする",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "を",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "る",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "す",
            "number": 5
          },
          {
            "value": "る",
            "number": 6
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "16f54ad7-56a8-473f-b1ab-638c1a04d553"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "をんど",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "を",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ど",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8e5c3adf-db79-4314-8d85-c00b4ad2ea55"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おをこす",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "を",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "す",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "437e9819-8524-435d-b6be-246086a954bb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かわ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9aec4f6f-a134-4304-a48d-a16c848dcc39"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "わかい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["わ", "を"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "32e3005d-7fdb-4430-a492-2c580e11621c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "n",
        "options": ["n"],
        "question": "ん"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ん"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f198d774-d0a1-4053-af72-cfa3c8a05b9c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ん",
        "options": ["ん"],
        "question": "n"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ん"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7596b06c-2f77-491b-bb29-35808c11e328"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ん",
            "rightSide": "n"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ん",
            "rightSide": "n"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ん"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "55b45a18-085c-45f3-a46d-7e906b742c34"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "n",
            "rightSide": "ん"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "n",
            "rightSide": "ん"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ん"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f098fc33-29d0-4729-9733-ab9955c3bccb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ほん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ほ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ん"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1d47e97d-9eb5-4f40-9e2c-df311ce8dfc3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "せんせい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "せ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "せ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ん"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2139ec27-46a0-49aa-a04f-67aaf65a736e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いんさつ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "つ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ん"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a4b9f1e5-b80a-445a-8a87-62578e83d599"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にんぎょう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ん"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "23a17704-6c87-4a37-a2d6-eb657f0d8290"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ga",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "が"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "47543f2b-5609-43ab-a807-b31ba52967ca"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gi",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "ぎ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "251a704c-61d9-4205-a040-d04ea3710ed9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gu",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "ぐ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d737af30-5900-48fc-8bd4-e61438c69d3e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ge",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "げ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "88a0eb8c-822e-423b-a6c2-79f8aeb02692"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "go",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "ご"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "aae51074-b5c8-4981-8365-761c0d29d139"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "が",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "ga"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3b97d8a6-69ce-4b0f-ae2e-02427461fbc3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎ",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "gi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "86c72736-3bf5-4374-ad25-4f8612d6f4ae"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぐ",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "gu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8eceda72-ee5d-4aa4-9270-1cbe491f6378"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "げ",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "ge"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f4e9a2b7-d17d-40ac-9df3-edf98d38565c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ご",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "go"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bb606837-f63f-4fec-84c4-3a3c050dd535"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "が",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "が"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d77e9218-ed07-4504-97c2-acdead1cb1d4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎ",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "ぎ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "df8c7c17-55c7-4c6e-aa6e-b67b876209c4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぐ",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "ぐ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5f4912a6-1346-467b-b4cf-18c057ff64af"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "げ",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "げ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2714d3d9-7203-4204-be54-67a9e10040ff"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ご",
        "options": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
        "question": "ご"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "636a0bb3-ab17-4272-8a68-5ad524d28798"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "が",
            "rightSide": "ga"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぎ",
            "rightSide": "gi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぐ",
            "rightSide": "gu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "げ",
            "rightSide": "ge"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ご",
            "rightSide": "go"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "が",
            "rightSide": "ga"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぎ",
            "rightSide": "gi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぐ",
            "rightSide": "gu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "げ",
            "rightSide": "ge"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ご",
            "rightSide": "go"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7b93b522-c965-427a-90b4-03e8aa8d8a2f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ga",
            "rightSide": "が"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gi",
            "rightSide": "ぎ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gu",
            "rightSide": "ぐ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ge",
            "rightSide": "げ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "go",
            "rightSide": "ご"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ga",
            "rightSide": "が"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gi",
            "rightSide": "ぎ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gu",
            "rightSide": "ぐ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ge",
            "rightSide": "げ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "go",
            "rightSide": "ご"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dfaaca84-dd4f-4f93-8f03-71e85067b94d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "がくせい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "せ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d05c41a6-7aae-4ffd-8db8-14b9865af041"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎんこう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1dbbbbc2-c892-49ba-ac83-413fd5a33629"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぐんたい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぐ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "た",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c0c8025e-a2d2-48f8-8821-fd14aac905ff"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "げんき",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "げ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5203807e-8e19-4dd2-be7a-b1e40d716aca"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ごはん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ご",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "は",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f588ffe3-8fce-4939-9a17-28c2e02af5fe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "まんが",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ま",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8658d010-25c2-423c-8c65-7acd1511d4b3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かがみ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4343272a-7023-44a2-bf33-4c5c0f8bbc4c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おんがく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "60095281-8de1-4316-a949-1209e9b17174"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にんぎょう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3c2f4593-b001-49d2-89f1-cc3b4ef89811"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "えいが",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["が", "ぎ", "ぐ", "げ", "ご"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cb698c34-f4ff-460b-a83e-846c4b0300e2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "za",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "ざ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3af8f9dc-69f5-4ac0-b078-58972c3d62dd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ji",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "じ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3ecc07af-604e-4a63-b0e9-264b99c64bb1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "zu",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "ず"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ea5d1107-2e18-4c6b-8b83-1ca7f0ab0308"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ze",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "ぜ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d0c2f933-9c63-4479-898c-6df8aab5d73e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "zo",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "ぞ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7e81ab9b-eaa1-4913-b24e-9d4063566865"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ざ",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "za"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3d66b117-7836-4d2a-9ae0-1eb94e80897a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じ",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "ji"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3abb5843-310c-452d-82e8-384ca0dff30d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ず",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "zu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8d30bde0-18aa-4c82-b3f7-364ab97ba71b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぜ",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "ze"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8d9f2980-204b-4f65-a8f1-08f1b9862b37"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぞ",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "zo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "92076fde-1c24-4f79-bd9f-8a04122d18cf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ざ",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "ざ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "59714e99-bed3-4603-865d-13ce85282750"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じ",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "じ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ee76c9d1-776b-4d39-be4e-35f4727072f0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ず",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "ず"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5e27a61c-f734-43e5-b94a-2d81055cc6b7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぜ",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "ぜ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4e569e9d-c6ae-4132-bd32-a76585d42c20"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぞ",
        "options": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
        "question": "ぞ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "21165b03-9644-4b79-8976-e9c763193123"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ざ",
            "rightSide": "za"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "じ",
            "rightSide": "ji"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ず",
            "rightSide": "zu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぜ",
            "rightSide": "ze"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぞ",
            "rightSide": "zo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ざ",
            "rightSide": "za"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "じ",
            "rightSide": "ji"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ず",
            "rightSide": "zu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぜ",
            "rightSide": "ze"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぞ",
            "rightSide": "zo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "405f1e09-8d10-4451-88d3-c9a2dc03bf1b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "za",
            "rightSide": "ざ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ji",
            "rightSide": "じ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zu",
            "rightSide": "ず"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ze",
            "rightSide": "ぜ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zo",
            "rightSide": "ぞ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "za",
            "rightSide": "ざ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ji",
            "rightSide": "じ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zu",
            "rightSide": "ず"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ze",
            "rightSide": "ぜ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zo",
            "rightSide": "ぞ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fa79cd4f-c2e9-430a-9ae6-8d96aa236cf8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ざっし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ざ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4c7831eb-f333-46f0-83a7-78f4cb72d7ce"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じしょ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cc0fd34e-aa72-4448-ad2b-15995a0524b8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ずこう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ず",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "995efb1f-d990-4e7c-a468-f479022bdf5f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぞう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぞ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "29c95d80-76d7-48fd-99e9-ebb572e4ae6b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かぞく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ぞ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "82d23f8c-4425-4576-9aed-bf78760e8d7d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じかん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6fbbd3cb-1eeb-4d8c-96a2-b4a6f385916a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ざる",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ざ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "る",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a7a21d8d-6c5e-4ba3-a0cb-ac77fab7a685"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぜんざい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぜ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ざ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "896371f8-0f2f-4b20-aff0-d5e5bb417d3a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じんこう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7619da8c-7aed-4c8e-b2f3-3fbe1924ca5b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "そうじ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "そ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ざ", "じ", "ず", "ぜ", "ぞ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4d5868f3-10fc-4d27-af13-0dbd812e8e40"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "da",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "だ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "90133f43-00f8-4e2b-aac8-59612c89f8a2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ji",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "ぢ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bc8e6c45-3516-4b4a-9980-8cc4c4052af5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "zu",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "づ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6411e3a9-9073-486b-82ad-76bc689eef0a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "de",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "で"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5ffee6a1-07bf-44fc-ab1e-0b625bed50f1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "do",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "ど"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a4296995-c8de-4508-8d56-b1b699f3f853"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "だ",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "da"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a4fea598-f898-4c4e-b059-81aa8b0dc24f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぢ",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "ji"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "be6d499a-51a6-4ce6-be9c-2d5a7114397e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "づ",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "zu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1afdaf3d-c4a3-477f-9237-86dde2eb0020"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "で",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "de"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "89aa1b4a-b810-4127-a6e4-ebbd6d213c3c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ど",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "do"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9da88922-59a7-432b-a1ff-70b7dc5e110b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "だ",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "だ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b897952f-9533-44ba-913b-544bc6831190"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぢ",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "ぢ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c32f23fd-0731-4582-9d4d-c53deedb4f05"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "づ",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "づ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b622aaf4-5bc5-4385-8120-6888bd286a75"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "で",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "で"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c0294727-cdae-4917-8889-a6faf47cae00"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ど",
        "options": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
        "question": "ど"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4c24bebb-2a10-445b-bb62-0ab61f833e09"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "だ",
            "rightSide": "da"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぢ",
            "rightSide": "ji"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "づ",
            "rightSide": "zu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "で",
            "rightSide": "de"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ど",
            "rightSide": "do"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "だ",
            "rightSide": "da"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぢ",
            "rightSide": "ji"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "づ",
            "rightSide": "zu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "で",
            "rightSide": "de"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ど",
            "rightSide": "do"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ac281a2b-907f-4ce7-804c-b28d3e5da93a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "da",
            "rightSide": "だ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ji",
            "rightSide": "ぢ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zu",
            "rightSide": "づ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "de",
            "rightSide": "で"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "do",
            "rightSide": "ど"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "da",
            "rightSide": "だ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ji",
            "rightSide": "ぢ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zu",
            "rightSide": "づ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "de",
            "rightSide": "で"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "do",
            "rightSide": "ど"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "79c6583c-7e97-472e-92d9-a1b100c7e1d7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "だいがく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "だ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a8154399-3e77-40e6-b185-050e7c451a53"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "でんわ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "で",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a7f35537-0590-4d89-9048-648d172909fa"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "どようび",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ど",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "よ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "び",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a2fa4f13-0611-4063-92cd-6bbdc6292caa"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "でぐち",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "で",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ぐ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bfbbf79b-8471-4c94-a7f6-97e0fca95dd7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "だんせい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "だ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "せ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6a37a228-0c6b-4014-b57c-53be93e00c09"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちず",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ず",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "37313ba3-ff0c-4f9a-bd2e-24a92ee89c10"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "でんしゃ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "で",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "29f05c2a-f859-4441-bfb3-ec414a6a108d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "どくしょ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ど",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "246fddb4-eeed-4522-9798-beacdf71ca5e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "たんご",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "た",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ご",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b6e4f651-bba4-449e-a2a5-7d08876d55fa"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "こづつみ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "づ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "つ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["だ", "ぢ", "づ", "で", "ど"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f4846f89-bfaf-49c2-8fe7-56607c5c48bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ba",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "ば"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0ad5d7de-ecd1-4c5c-8ed5-125704190042"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "bi",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "び"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "74b4b5d7-1b45-4c4c-bf6f-4d9a8ce90f67"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "bu",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "ぶ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f94bbf9b-6fa7-467a-86b6-3d77d9d68631"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "be",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "べ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "20068b61-dc1c-4213-b11e-cd4c8310b448"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "bo",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "ぼ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "31a4a41e-fed7-4bd1-9976-396324c0394c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ば",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "ba"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "25bdff4b-df81-4c27-b8f4-2cd13c5aed1d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "び",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "bi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "15ecbc59-fa77-42a8-9a21-47a00c9a1dff"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぶ",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "bu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "334cc54f-314a-455d-ab66-4ff1166b115c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "べ",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "be"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "44f9786d-3b70-4c94-a46f-bb76886448bd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぼ",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "bo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6bad7f51-240a-4300-9f8d-2c365da37bb4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ば",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "ば"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a2d0ba56-ee4d-4c59-9256-013855ca33bd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "び",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "び"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1f99149f-972d-4f3c-afb9-0656aefc1fdb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぶ",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "ぶ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e5f24616-f26c-4230-84fe-05cd0fbd1780"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "べ",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "べ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3d8e0dca-6e3f-45ed-964a-67af6c6273b1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぼ",
        "options": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
        "question": "ぼ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d2191381-909e-4550-8091-548f4efb1b96"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ば",
            "rightSide": "ba"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "び",
            "rightSide": "bi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぶ",
            "rightSide": "bu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "べ",
            "rightSide": "be"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぼ",
            "rightSide": "bo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ば",
            "rightSide": "ba"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "び",
            "rightSide": "bi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぶ",
            "rightSide": "bu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "べ",
            "rightSide": "be"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぼ",
            "rightSide": "bo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ae61612e-0678-44d5-9a51-ad0cf6b6bbe9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ba",
            "rightSide": "ば"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bi",
            "rightSide": "び"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bu",
            "rightSide": "ぶ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "be",
            "rightSide": "べ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bo",
            "rightSide": "ぼ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ba",
            "rightSide": "ば"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bi",
            "rightSide": "び"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bu",
            "rightSide": "ぶ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "be",
            "rightSide": "べ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bo",
            "rightSide": "ぼ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a28960e6-b476-4f8f-8c88-ca19c8312f4f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ばしょ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ば",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "aaee4855-c3bb-4b1f-99e4-88cd5150bbd0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びょういん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "び",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8d0e4189-6b9e-41d9-9971-7b0bc9c727b2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぶんか",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぶ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bb68cdc2-8885-4b87-bfd7-9644c65a7d04"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "べんきょう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "べ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "56c06a07-d520-4769-a7e8-036b96caec73"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぼうし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぼ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "86c5adf5-7f1d-498e-84cb-4f3cbdaf462a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "あそぶ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "そ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぶ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "929ced70-7dea-4fc3-82d3-b11536247652"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "さべつ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "べ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "つ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1bcde735-ad25-4b1f-a655-9c094d83e6c1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しんぶん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぶ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bcf3573b-8e3b-4e13-b4d8-b0b19e65bcc2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "てぶくろ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "て",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ぶ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ろ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ec5d5424-5b9e-43a1-a881-843fc0ad1fda"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぶたにく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぶ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "た",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ば", "び", "ぶ", "べ", "ぼ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5900f8f2-f90e-4af6-8e7f-2090fa18b1a7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pa",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "ぱ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a736a227-c9f6-485c-813f-47d1144a0fab"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pi",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "ぴ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a556a7cf-4d33-41de-977b-d98c7e1d5b15"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pu",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "ぷ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b9649f8d-7f26-4b6e-af92-4768294e4c4d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pe",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "ぺ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e737c742-0a34-49f7-8f57-91bc3da023e2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "po",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "ぽ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bd579742-05b5-4bcc-aa30-9f93fbf46b6c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぱ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "pa"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bbc9b8bb-c88c-40d3-aa47-5f5a3a2206ee"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "pi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5d715ba3-e7cb-48b1-80d9-a8c2975c74e2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぷ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "pu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b9f49aa9-f97a-42e6-ac96-981026d4db80"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぺ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "pe"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "28223d52-db36-477c-bd7d-106d6bf8a54c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぽ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "po"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7b68a603-f15e-4e4e-b387-ffedeb7ef1c9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぱ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "ぱ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3d006613-6420-46b2-bb67-105d1eec28f5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "ぴ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "354c78ef-473c-4833-ba95-2a6d819ff3a1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぷ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "ぷ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "12a1a78a-fd4c-445f-9e42-6fc0181c77c4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぺ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "ぺ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "94e3c4dd-df4e-443d-9cd2-9f6d012e5c57"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぽ",
        "options": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
        "question": "ぽ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2d881162-cd10-44d3-a8ee-a26235f04335"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ぱ",
            "rightSide": "pa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぴ",
            "rightSide": "pi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぷ",
            "rightSide": "pu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぺ",
            "rightSide": "pe"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぽ",
            "rightSide": "po"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ぱ",
            "rightSide": "pa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぴ",
            "rightSide": "pi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぷ",
            "rightSide": "pu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぺ",
            "rightSide": "pe"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぽ",
            "rightSide": "po"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5346c215-e937-4e45-9c07-d0ea8b01b619"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "pa",
            "rightSide": "ぱ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pi",
            "rightSide": "ぴ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pu",
            "rightSide": "ぷ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pe",
            "rightSide": "ぺ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "po",
            "rightSide": "ぽ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "pa",
            "rightSide": "ぱ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pi",
            "rightSide": "ぴ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pu",
            "rightSide": "ぷ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pe",
            "rightSide": "ぺ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "po",
            "rightSide": "ぽ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "04e177d1-e1ac-4c9a-ac2d-6461d5eeeea0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぱん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぱ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f77ebe4c-9ce4-497e-ae20-294181b96fb9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴか",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぴ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ffa93e01-ef87-4874-922e-8fab56f375ef"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぷち",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぷ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "41ae6742-15fb-4ded-889b-72a2c4609620"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぺこ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぺ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "617beb7c-bf3c-4812-a045-e198d962423d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぽすと",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぽ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "す",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f02384b0-f529-41ad-bb08-532d4980365c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "さんぽ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぽ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "177e660d-b183-4644-8519-7400591e387f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "てんぷら",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "て",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぷ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ら",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6e8d5d46-04ca-44f9-85b4-849f4a378401"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひっぱる",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ひ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぱ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "る",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f956f5d2-ec5c-43dd-950d-8e7708560250"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しんぱい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぱ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cbcdcbe3-8e7d-48b3-84b3-f330474e7389"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "はっぱ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "は",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぱ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぱ", "ぴ", "ぷ", "ぺ", "ぽ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "12bf1474-1995-4d28-9cb8-5ac70b39e393"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "kya",
        "options": ["kya", "kyu", "kyo"],
        "question": "きゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6499f0e7-7929-40a7-ab91-f94346474240"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "kyu",
        "options": ["kya", "kyu", "kyo"],
        "question": "きゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "faf7f266-ae4f-4d36-9b60-b6545bd5dc5a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "kyo",
        "options": ["kya", "kyu", "kyo"],
        "question": "きょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f955a350-46cf-40e7-b6fe-3772dc2e66fc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きゃ",
        "options": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
        "question": "kya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f188e020-523e-44e1-b41e-070eaa00ff5e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きゅ",
        "options": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
        "question": "kyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "85ffa9b1-741a-4915-8b95-50a8a67f4d43"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きょ",
        "options": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
        "question": "kyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0a8774e2-23a6-4094-9a00-866bb077909a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きゃ",
        "options": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
        "question": "きゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dff0ab2b-899a-47a7-9b39-f55ac7257348"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きゅ",
        "options": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
        "question": "きゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7f6a5b96-25bb-4977-9a45-a27a272f6394"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きょ",
        "options": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
        "question": "きょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d200a13f-55a3-46b1-97c2-a56263ea96c4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "きゃ",
            "rightSide": "kya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "きゅ",
            "rightSide": "kyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "きょ",
            "rightSide": "kyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "きゃ",
            "rightSide": "kya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "きゅ",
            "rightSide": "kyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "きょ",
            "rightSide": "kyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "199fd28a-5ce3-46fa-a61b-ac8c09bc3018"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "kya",
            "rightSide": "きゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "kyu",
            "rightSide": "きゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "kyo",
            "rightSide": "きょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "kya",
            "rightSide": "きゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "kyu",
            "rightSide": "きゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "kyo",
            "rightSide": "きょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1c54fe27-2bbc-4d93-9e97-1d51eddbe5a5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きゃく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "125a7c16-ef0a-4d3e-88bf-41161fd83cde"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きゅうけい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "39105c10-0fdd-4163-9374-702d61c69269"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きょうしつ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "つ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c0b7ced9-4585-4a1d-8664-ad9dfbf65c1e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しんきょ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2ef9632a-0760-4f13-9bb8-6a8c2181812b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にんぎょう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7b29fe95-c3a1-4505-a77c-961314c8d1ec"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gya",
        "options": ["gya", "gyu", "gyo"],
        "question": "ぎゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "06629aa1-da60-42d6-bdf3-a9a341f40ad8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gyu",
        "options": ["gya", "gyu", "gyo"],
        "question": "ぎゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "eb4fb19c-f62b-45cb-a7b5-1d61e16b40ca"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gyo",
        "options": ["gya", "gyu", "gyo"],
        "question": "ぎょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "028ae92e-555a-45b7-a4a5-08f906a6840b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎゃ",
        "options": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
        "question": "gya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4ada81a0-0b24-4fdf-9d62-6aab20e5e21a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎゅ",
        "options": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
        "question": "gyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "94b75138-7e5d-4bf6-863b-93e94fbb18f6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎょ",
        "options": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
        "question": "gyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3d7c4d20-3422-44f9-9282-8e4936eccc79"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎゃ",
        "options": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
        "question": "ぎゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "29bf212c-d3b8-4b57-be03-c544bd7d9599"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎゅ",
        "options": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
        "question": "ぎゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ab983b08-1b4b-43f8-8b72-8c02e9dd288a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎょ",
        "options": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
        "question": "ぎょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "297b6403-b9dc-46cb-9ec5-ae5d51d3d59a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ぎゃ",
            "rightSide": "gya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぎゅ",
            "rightSide": "gyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぎょ",
            "rightSide": "gyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ぎゃ",
            "rightSide": "gya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぎゅ",
            "rightSide": "gyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぎょ",
            "rightSide": "gyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0f91dbea-a3a9-4a09-b361-d21ef3e78e78"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "gya",
            "rightSide": "ぎゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gyu",
            "rightSide": "ぎゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gyo",
            "rightSide": "ぎょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "gya",
            "rightSide": "ぎゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gyu",
            "rightSide": "ぎゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gyo",
            "rightSide": "ぎょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fce35190-f30c-4f61-8b19-0dde7c79e1e3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎゃく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "42e4f45a-fafd-4d89-b32a-d15f1026a66b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎゅうにゅう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8c1e86e7-cbe8-4e42-87f8-b529b57c4b55"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎょぎょう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e5a89530-73c3-4360-85a8-e1f93d599f77"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎゃっこう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "23d2132c-060d-4c89-a2ae-4b40c6cba066"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぎょかいるい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "る",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぎゃ", "ぎゅ", "ぎょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "02a4c691-e030-401d-b711-86744a445348"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "sha",
        "options": ["sha", "shu", "sho"],
        "question": "しゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b3f2c71b-805e-4fb4-a638-12d636af58ff"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "shu",
        "options": ["sha", "shu", "sho"],
        "question": "しゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c0615f09-911d-41a3-9ecf-e82dcd37725d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "sho",
        "options": ["sha", "shu", "sho"],
        "question": "しょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f4614c4f-f360-4125-8acd-50fd794632dc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しゃ",
        "options": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
        "question": "sha"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a25c9823-31fd-4c2b-8a1c-de454122cf5a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しゅ",
        "options": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
        "question": "shu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c7c7dbbd-35bf-4745-aff6-392419565fdf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しょ",
        "options": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
        "question": "sho"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b136044a-40ea-43a6-9a7d-35a2fd0be537"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しゃ",
        "options": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
        "question": "しゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "147c6b17-a4c5-4882-8f03-b902fb9990ea"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しゅ",
        "options": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
        "question": "しゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "97fbdf9b-0e43-4bcc-b39a-19133cab0ed5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しょ",
        "options": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
        "question": "しょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "69945db5-1410-4b7c-b299-64254aafe861"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "しゃ",
            "rightSide": "sha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "しゅ",
            "rightSide": "shu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "しょ",
            "rightSide": "sho"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "しゃ",
            "rightSide": "sha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "しゅ",
            "rightSide": "shu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "しょ",
            "rightSide": "sho"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dd45eb44-140d-40f1-8b26-b9dad3e0e3a4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "sha",
            "rightSide": "しゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "shu",
            "rightSide": "しゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "sho",
            "rightSide": "しょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "sha",
            "rightSide": "しゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "shu",
            "rightSide": "しゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "sho",
            "rightSide": "しょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "25f1da40-3e34-4b7f-b2b9-18f81f49a9a0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しゃしん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1b6327c4-e7d0-4302-9b83-61fb15400248"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しゅくだい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "だ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "368bd0af-28e6-46eb-b6f4-9e301c9d36af"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しょうがっこう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 5
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 6
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f038d801-e8fa-4275-956d-1e3144f2f31d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "でんしゃ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "で",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "66f7cef8-6f9f-48e2-9624-6eba9b77d69e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かいしゃ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "07542c4e-e37b-424e-a618-0f601bd8fad4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ja",
        "options": ["ja", "ju", "jo"],
        "question": "じゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3ce02b45-0aba-4746-8fbf-8923a4b3603e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ju",
        "options": ["ja", "ju", "jo"],
        "question": "じゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9e39c773-3487-41fd-8abc-8be0e81f4515"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "jo",
        "options": ["ja", "ju", "jo"],
        "question": "じょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3322f165-638e-4c2a-b0b7-153f55461bf1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じゃ",
        "options": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
        "question": "ja"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ca98d33a-a8c2-486a-85ac-5222cd31c9e6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じゅ",
        "options": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
        "question": "ju"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4182a90a-3d06-41e9-9ab7-c0dcae9fa226"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じょ",
        "options": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
        "question": "jo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c7c6ca94-4dff-4484-a7a8-f424e51c19f2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じゃ",
        "options": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
        "question": "じゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "88c2762f-a76f-4888-a6a7-9c1b2acc90ab"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じゅ",
        "options": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
        "question": "じゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b7591ffc-6ff3-41a3-b430-8d3a00bf841d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じょ",
        "options": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
        "question": "じょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9e86c2b6-0b9a-481f-bf09-6744baee1274"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "じゃ",
            "rightSide": "ja"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "じゅ",
            "rightSide": "ju"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "じょ",
            "rightSide": "jo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "じゃ",
            "rightSide": "ja"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "じゅ",
            "rightSide": "ju"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "じょ",
            "rightSide": "jo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e2a48624-8419-43ce-9bc4-42cd05717327"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ja",
            "rightSide": "じゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ju",
            "rightSide": "じゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "jo",
            "rightSide": "じょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ja",
            "rightSide": "じゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ju",
            "rightSide": "じゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "jo",
            "rightSide": "じょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "efe59a33-a70f-4df3-b114-1e88cf41fda6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じゅぎょう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "964a28e6-a623-46b5-a978-aaad34b68fbb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じょうぎ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ぎ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e398ecc9-c455-491b-a350-7a0bfdd4ed5c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "かいじょ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5a5516e8-011c-4a90-867d-a0e26da8e637"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びじゅつかん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "び",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "つ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e26ab124-8e0b-44ff-a3d0-df5824cf3ba8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "じゃんけん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["じゃ", "じゅ", "じょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d453c405-2082-4782-ad60-c0c92acd091e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "cha",
        "options": ["cha", "chu", "cho"],
        "question": "ちゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c6aae3da-3586-46bd-b85c-1ab42cfb7e7c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "chu",
        "options": ["cha", "chu", "cho"],
        "question": "ちゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "74f31036-d0e0-4b3f-aee1-f6f2503700b3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "cho",
        "options": ["cha", "chu", "cho"],
        "question": "ちょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ea2d8025-77a7-406d-9683-712e3bb322ae"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちゃ",
        "options": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
        "question": "cha"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "11e2ae2a-ddfc-48b9-aa3e-c900165b5cc0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちゅ",
        "options": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
        "question": "chu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d1292075-b15f-4950-a153-471bc05f8859"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちょ",
        "options": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
        "question": "cho"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "50f02ea7-ce86-43db-b128-ac32115428c0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちゃ",
        "options": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
        "question": "ちゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "be2e21ce-5dbd-4340-b72e-fa85d2f583dd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちゅ",
        "options": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
        "question": "ちゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ce48dec7-f360-449f-b668-0271bb8a3f0e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちょ",
        "options": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
        "question": "ちょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "10c2f799-2860-4529-923d-6297449f7b6d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ちゃ",
            "rightSide": "cha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ちゅ",
            "rightSide": "chu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ちょ",
            "rightSide": "cho"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ちゃ",
            "rightSide": "cha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ちゅ",
            "rightSide": "chu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ちょ",
            "rightSide": "cho"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "65682d0a-2107-4819-826a-e8bcde5152f2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "cha",
            "rightSide": "ちゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "chu",
            "rightSide": "ちゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "cho",
            "rightSide": "ちょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "cha",
            "rightSide": "ちゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "chu",
            "rightSide": "ちゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "cho",
            "rightSide": "ちょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3271a10e-f695-4717-af50-e12e584e4fdb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びょ",
        "options": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
        "question": "byo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "674840bb-7868-48d2-bf8b-914679791b6c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちゅうしゃ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "21eaa144-d408-4126-8735-e7b247799e40"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちょきん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bd620785-bb78-4f62-8cf8-88d2d3dcdf04"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちゃわん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "わ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d071079a-b480-4811-b99d-a48bfd508b79"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちゅうがく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "301d4472-a5e9-416e-abc9-fcf62d187e1f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちょくせつ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "せ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "つ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6d8b9124-3b3d-4bd5-ae87-9830996b07b6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "nya",
        "options": ["nya", "nyu", "nyo"],
        "question": "にゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9d1b74d2-2652-4309-9155-9235a99f2448"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "nyu",
        "options": ["nya", "nyu", "nyo"],
        "question": "にゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9c466732-9848-4d8b-908b-9a512149f436"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "nyo",
        "options": ["nya", "nyu", "nyo"],
        "question": "にょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1ff661a0-9852-4494-bbe7-ce988ef5046a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にゃ",
        "options": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
        "question": "nya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cc094002-c8f5-4e99-a475-843206c1df66"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にゅ",
        "options": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
        "question": "nyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3bcf7561-ea91-44cf-b9aa-0db903992e03"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にょ",
        "options": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
        "question": "nyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c85ef17b-cafd-4c32-b2d6-b14ea89064ce"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にゃ",
        "options": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
        "question": "にゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0a7dac4a-4fa3-4d02-984c-ef82c46a9fc3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にゅ",
        "options": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
        "question": "にゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9114b301-e442-4b57-90ed-ca7ae12727dc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にょ",
        "options": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
        "question": "にょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7a195c7a-443a-4438-8250-a93312f4beed"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "にゃ",
            "rightSide": "nya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "にゅ",
            "rightSide": "nyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "にょ",
            "rightSide": "nyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "にゃ",
            "rightSide": "nya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "にゅ",
            "rightSide": "nyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "にょ",
            "rightSide": "nyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "13c4467e-f45a-4794-b137-916edd050c53"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "nya",
            "rightSide": "にゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nyu",
            "rightSide": "にゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nyo",
            "rightSide": "にょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "nya",
            "rightSide": "にゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nyu",
            "rightSide": "にゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nyo",
            "rightSide": "にょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9db99ea6-59a7-4599-9811-13bcd15071f9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にゃんこ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "aab3baa0-1b46-4def-a527-76370626b816"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にゅういん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0b69fc0a-9f9f-4dd8-ab09-b4c003f90669"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にょじつ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "つ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "84c5ae9c-b22b-4b8b-b59c-d5eeca4714a9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にゅうがく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "815ed9a4-e7ce-4500-a974-39ee61948f38"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びゃ",
        "options": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
        "question": "びゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4953aa22-7dc0-46f3-967b-9060c82843a6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "にょろにょろ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ろ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ろ",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "89c821a1-a8e6-4969-89a6-44e0b588934b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "hya",
        "options": ["hya", "hyu", "hyo"],
        "question": "ひゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "17a53bbb-65fd-40cb-ac08-8a24cd3f10f1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "hyu",
        "options": ["hya", "hyu", "hyo"],
        "question": "ひゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7248f22f-9635-4930-b0e3-be05366fa7c9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "hyo",
        "options": ["hya", "hyu", "hyo"],
        "question": "ひょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b9c8c7a7-f4cb-40a2-80a2-842f4e2cdeee"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひゃ",
        "options": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
        "question": "hya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2f1b0f18-0d66-470a-8605-0f7733416d11"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひゅ",
        "options": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
        "question": "hyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bdfce23b-7707-4439-ab48-3e071c981e2a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひょ",
        "options": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
        "question": "hyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "076b867f-19dc-4759-bd31-4ea4c23ee1b5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひゃ",
        "options": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
        "question": "ひゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "261c0924-bde9-4e2f-be9c-6fd6f4a3f067"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひゅ",
        "options": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
        "question": "ひゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8721d2c8-be1c-4095-a021-13fe1b437e20"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひょ",
        "options": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
        "question": "ひょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "192e69d9-512c-41a2-85cd-3f254f573edc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ひゃ",
            "rightSide": "hya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ひゅ",
            "rightSide": "hyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ひょ",
            "rightSide": "hyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ひゃ",
            "rightSide": "hya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ひゅ",
            "rightSide": "hyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ひょ",
            "rightSide": "hyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5394f81d-431f-426d-9d7b-19a00060c491"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "hya",
            "rightSide": "ひゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hyu",
            "rightSide": "ひゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hyo",
            "rightSide": "ひょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "hya",
            "rightSide": "ひゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hyu",
            "rightSide": "ひゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hyo",
            "rightSide": "ひょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "202eefcb-26f8-4469-8799-140b80332497"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひゃくえん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ひ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5e5bd9f0-f168-48bb-8d9a-f452b0746571"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひゅうが",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ひ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a544107f-6876-44af-94ec-440c170c9391"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひょうご",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ひ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ご",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d520715a-b8ad-45f7-b05b-47b802150968"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひゃくにん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ひ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "に",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d4ab5831-e490-4c78-bef0-b2e96f48e22b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ひょうしき",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ひ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2cbe43a8-d50c-4279-9a92-2cd21e3c060f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "bya",
        "options": ["bya", "byu", "byo"],
        "question": "びゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ba19e4f7-beb7-4af3-be7c-20affbacc09c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "byu",
        "options": ["bya", "byu", "byo"],
        "question": "びゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "55a81b9f-8ad6-4f08-98b1-748bae3688b4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "byo",
        "options": ["bya", "byu", "byo"],
        "question": "びょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "691a4e92-9a51-4724-82e6-e2c7696169d5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びゃ",
        "options": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
        "question": "bya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "68a0d59f-17e6-4608-842e-b9881a6a3dc3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びゅ",
        "options": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
        "question": "byu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5594788d-d55f-42fc-9271-13ffb9d28a73"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びゅ",
        "options": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
        "question": "びゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bc83501f-baeb-4d8d-8887-f56b4c3bc881"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びょ",
        "options": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
        "question": "びょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "faca465b-8650-4841-be04-fb8c208ee784"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "びゃ",
            "rightSide": "bya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "びゅ",
            "rightSide": "byu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "びょ",
            "rightSide": "byo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "びゃ",
            "rightSide": "bya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "びゅ",
            "rightSide": "byu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "びょ",
            "rightSide": "byo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e4a30f26-f6cd-4464-baae-e9fe6457fed8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "bya",
            "rightSide": "びゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "byu",
            "rightSide": "びゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "byo",
            "rightSide": "びょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "bya",
            "rightSide": "びゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "byu",
            "rightSide": "びゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "byo",
            "rightSide": "びょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8ef020fb-4067-46f0-a1ea-dd28c6af2ee6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びょういん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "び",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f3dbb4d4-dbca-4f6e-9f34-95e6c0973421"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びゅういん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "び",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a32c7436-0318-45b6-b380-21b7e6d0c655"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びょうき",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "び",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4361346b-6b91-476c-8564-dd3474c8d584"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びょうどう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "び",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ど",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e52f0ddd-d8e2-404f-9b8e-68c857b2efdc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "びゃっこ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "び",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "05e8c573-0abd-4c2f-9007-2bf62e9ee169"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pya",
        "options": ["pya", "pyu", "pyo"],
        "question": "ぴゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "792cecb6-60f1-4a21-bc12-cca1c45f78c5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pyu",
        "options": ["pya", "pyu", "pyo"],
        "question": "ぴゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "938b5a4a-f79e-479e-a4b7-756d5e246d3e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pyo",
        "options": ["pya", "pyu", "pyo"],
        "question": "ぴょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "73111bdb-d32a-40f2-b2d7-433b0e3641af"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴゃ",
        "options": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
        "question": "pya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f6a91620-2c72-4eb9-9cf7-db013d7761c7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴゅ",
        "options": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
        "question": "pyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7c948e8e-2aae-4230-bfb3-e042da7ffac3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴょ",
        "options": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
        "question": "pyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "095e466c-4a92-4b9e-8d71-e7bd1863adef"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴゃ",
        "options": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
        "question": "ぴゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "98f76c60-6a2a-40fa-a213-c543b9659917"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴゅ",
        "options": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
        "question": "ぴゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9aea1da4-fd3d-4a00-9e54-c562ad3fa4fc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴょ",
        "options": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
        "question": "ぴょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "43cf052f-afe6-4adc-964f-e777d137a4db"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ぴゃ",
            "rightSide": "pya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぴゅ",
            "rightSide": "pyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぴょ",
            "rightSide": "pyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ぴゃ",
            "rightSide": "pya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぴゅ",
            "rightSide": "pyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ぴょ",
            "rightSide": "pyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cfc9758c-f646-49f3-94f0-d0cc59364b47"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "pya",
            "rightSide": "ぴゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pyu",
            "rightSide": "ぴゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pyo",
            "rightSide": "ぴょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "pya",
            "rightSide": "ぴゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pyu",
            "rightSide": "ぴゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pyo",
            "rightSide": "ぴょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "46457fae-9473-41d9-b101-4b358338224f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "っ+t",
        "options": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
        "question": "tt"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "99ffc0df-379f-4cb9-aac4-2f3652325162"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴょんぴょん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぴ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ぴ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2812a30a-34bd-4be0-9e2c-7f1c433951c1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴょこぴょこ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぴ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ぴ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0ac79210-e78f-46c4-97aa-190722ae8018"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴゅうぴゅう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぴ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ぴ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a64b17d9-0afe-4064-9e3a-c24bce31e1bd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴゃっと",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぴ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c5f43a7c-8274-478d-a6f6-9549ae95ada4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ぴょんた",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ぴ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "た",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ぴゃ", "ぴゅ", "ぴょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "982fdd52-464f-47c9-a41b-7d9934878fb6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "mya",
        "options": ["mya", "myu", "myo"],
        "question": "みゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d6e3b194-6d4e-43d4-adcf-fc44fd2bac42"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "myu",
        "options": ["mya", "myu", "myo"],
        "question": "みゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6d3283c1-b2d6-468b-86bc-647184a9de35"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "myo",
        "options": ["mya", "myu", "myo"],
        "question": "みょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2d45b5a4-20d9-46b1-b0b3-792e59ff5bc3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みゃ",
        "options": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
        "question": "mya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "adf69186-4886-47d9-86c0-1e8b39f85e53"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みゅ",
        "options": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
        "question": "myu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9ddee84f-9133-4083-9db9-1540668e4f42"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みょ",
        "options": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
        "question": "myo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9cab0dd5-873b-4be2-84c8-dd24dd087796"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みゃ",
        "options": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
        "question": "みゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0e536835-0809-490f-8ebb-9fc8e0f70389"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みゅ",
        "options": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
        "question": "みゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c4d2379b-b2ce-491d-a7cc-38185e93c577"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みょ",
        "options": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
        "question": "みょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "70f57ffa-a64a-4417-8217-135ea40ec9e3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "みゃ",
            "rightSide": "mya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "みゅ",
            "rightSide": "myu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "みょ",
            "rightSide": "myo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "みゃ",
            "rightSide": "mya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "みゅ",
            "rightSide": "myu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "みょ",
            "rightSide": "myo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8f4fb945-69ff-4aac-ae3a-2e5e65b37e93"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "mya",
            "rightSide": "みゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "myu",
            "rightSide": "みゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "myo",
            "rightSide": "みょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "mya",
            "rightSide": "みゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "myu",
            "rightSide": "みゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "myo",
            "rightSide": "みょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3c0c808c-f806-4252-8059-aaac2e83c353"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みゃく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "631b7d7a-0658-4e8f-bb17-831e23aa7b32"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みょうじ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "じ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5367e93a-c9aa-4a1b-8aea-a1c373378bec"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みょうが",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8a171832-1289-4ec7-be4c-5776c1397c2d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みゅう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0ac2344c-c008-4751-a2b2-791da895e2bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "っ+p",
        "options": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
        "question": "pp"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3b9b8176-a240-404f-801b-c040df5631bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "みゃあみゃあ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "み",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f72659c1-fd7b-4cb1-a32f-5f53b424912e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "rya",
        "options": ["rya", "ryu", "ryo"],
        "question": "りゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d8164987-b306-4b68-ac6f-3650dc34c8e5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ryu",
        "options": ["rya", "ryu", "ryo"],
        "question": "りゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f6836f95-db14-4ff4-831e-26052e021ea6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ryo",
        "options": ["rya", "ryu", "ryo"],
        "question": "りょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "53cd460c-9b1e-4698-a0a0-f7790553a959"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りゃ",
        "options": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
        "question": "rya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "123ec5a5-3fba-4e99-8131-9d4f7798df6f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りゅ",
        "options": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
        "question": "ryu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a957ba92-7dbe-4fad-96e1-3ff0b8b07d61"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りょ",
        "options": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
        "question": "ryo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "871cd25d-b499-4aba-9fb8-2ffc40d70a8c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りゃ",
        "options": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
        "question": "りゃ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3541c45d-fabd-440d-8252-49e1d2e89335"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りゅ",
        "options": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
        "question": "りゅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "89fd4168-18f5-41e8-bc1d-183caae70aeb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りょ",
        "options": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
        "question": "りょ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "90a58c03-7759-4e1a-9e37-79d3b477e3fc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "りゃ",
            "rightSide": "rya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "りゅ",
            "rightSide": "ryu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "りょ",
            "rightSide": "ryo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "りゃ",
            "rightSide": "rya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "りゅ",
            "rightSide": "ryu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "りょ",
            "rightSide": "ryo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3860341a-1c94-4af5-87cc-9a55f3781f92"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "rya",
            "rightSide": "りゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ryu",
            "rightSide": "りゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ryo",
            "rightSide": "りょ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "rya",
            "rightSide": "りゃ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ryu",
            "rightSide": "りゅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ryo",
            "rightSide": "りょ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "89a2b950-a783-498b-a2de-8f8d36342218"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りゃく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "り",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c3120d6d-feba-4160-b73f-59af60739ff1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りゅう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "り",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2069d104-b59d-41bd-88fe-928daac28dd2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りょこう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "り",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "39a13ffe-0e0b-4d09-a4fa-7ae2cc44ce5c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りゅうがく",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "り",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゅ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "59de95de-9ff1-4cff-9cf4-5846d9520ea0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "りょくちゃ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "り",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "く",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ゃ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "801a0db7-9653-4ef5-8d41-5773ca56fbac"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "kk",
        "options": ["kk", "ss", "tt", "pp"],
        "question": "っ+k"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6ef4532b-0e9e-434b-8032-6f9c181c8df0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ss",
        "options": ["kk", "ss", "tt", "pp"],
        "question": "っ+s"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "be3cec20-4596-472c-b478-bcc355e675c2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "tt",
        "options": ["kk", "ss", "tt", "pp"],
        "question": "っ+t"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6dc77054-b6a2-4ebf-8c28-e4eb7e320d61"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pp",
        "options": ["kk", "ss", "tt", "pp"],
        "question": "っ+p"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7842aacc-1803-42d2-bb2c-33aefd82360b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "っ+k",
        "options": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
        "question": "kk"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "df2b7734-87ef-44f9-a16e-5c43dcf3b4c0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "っ+s",
        "options": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
        "question": "ss"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "79d06904-ea5f-4d94-9dc4-505e0251fc40"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "っ+k",
        "options": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
        "question": "っ+k"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2a5e0f09-e24a-4206-b4d3-9cafe74e2721"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "っ+s",
        "options": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
        "question": "っ+s"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5af4b07f-0af5-48ff-8d95-4279e3e80235"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "っ+t",
        "options": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
        "question": "っ+t"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2bea6120-128c-4feb-b59a-819d7bcd8470"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "っ+p",
        "options": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
        "question": "っ+p"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cec1cc20-4bc4-49b6-a6ce-50454d0fe779"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "っ+k",
            "rightSide": "kk"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "っ+s",
            "rightSide": "ss"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "っ+t",
            "rightSide": "tt"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "っ+p",
            "rightSide": "pp"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "っ+k",
            "rightSide": "kk"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "っ+s",
            "rightSide": "ss"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "っ+t",
            "rightSide": "tt"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "っ+p",
            "rightSide": "pp"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "06deac38-de9e-41fd-aced-dab2d371f8fa"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "kk",
            "rightSide": "っ+k"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ss",
            "rightSide": "っ+s"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "tt",
            "rightSide": "っ+t"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pp",
            "rightSide": "っ+p"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "kk",
            "rightSide": "っ+k"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ss",
            "rightSide": "っ+s"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "tt",
            "rightSide": "っ+t"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pp",
            "rightSide": "っ+p"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "16a94267-bd5b-47f1-82b5-0a86eb3412f9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きって",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "て",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d25ee18c-4bc4-419d-a0f2-1d0ff48857c0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "けっこん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4bc6c118-e21d-4216-a7c8-04ad0e8e838d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "がっこう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "が",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "096a56cb-f793-4966-827c-8c63da40e870"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ざっし",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ざ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "649cc27f-fbdc-4258-a63d-5012e4f985f0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ちょっかん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ち",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ょ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "か",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ce59bc50-0fa9-482d-95ff-cd8d82ed3f40"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いっぽ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぽ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6690cbcf-350e-40f3-8c5d-8ebdeae9133f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "やっぱり",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "や",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぱ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "り",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "de4e17c6-a34e-4085-9aa0-673fae0df93e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "きっぷ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぷ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "416c32bf-f937-4819-addf-813a83a9ddbe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "さっぱり",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぱ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "り",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d145ab98-25b6-4272-8e90-10a9b4a5b46e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "しっぱい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "し",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "っ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぱ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["っ+k", "っ+s", "っ+t", "っ+p"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a810eeb6-f2ea-4e6f-a8f7-8138ba0744bf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "aa",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "ああ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cc0aa6f4-d6ab-4737-8315-bdd577b4adda"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ii",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "いい"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "76468a9c-11bb-4fa2-b855-cd5af0fb5de1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "uu",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "うう"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "359c9da7-8ca6-457d-a9d4-1f14973e5997"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ee",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "ええ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b1132d5d-b666-4b7b-aa23-f6ee0c126c77"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "oo",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "おお"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "603ece54-1f27-4d3d-a5d5-3714d8380334"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ああ",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "aa"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7a8ff800-be9d-494e-af69-92353c751111"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いい",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "ii"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7341ab1c-45f4-4b01-99ae-cdb4e3448429"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "うう",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "uu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "416022a0-44f1-4b29-ab78-32c26e84a957"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ええ",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "ee"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c49e1479-2ce9-47cc-958d-a948a1c9af18"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おお",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "oo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ec22aa12-0f89-46b9-b8a8-18a70696a09d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ああ",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "ああ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a829021f-2b2a-4a9a-bc3d-ff9540a7851e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いい",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "いい"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d78589d9-c4d9-4514-93b4-261508b17eea"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "うう",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "うう"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "94d23bac-c5b4-4ffe-b80e-2136105d7249"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ええ",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "ええ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f5f646c4-6efb-4db3-bb3a-3b45d58f84f8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おお",
        "options": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
        "question": "おお"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b5e000d3-7ebd-4570-a1f5-47fd580ce30e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ああ",
            "rightSide": "aa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "いい",
            "rightSide": "ii"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "うう",
            "rightSide": "uu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ええ",
            "rightSide": "ee"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "おお",
            "rightSide": "oo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ああ",
            "rightSide": "aa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "いい",
            "rightSide": "ii"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "うう",
            "rightSide": "uu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ええ",
            "rightSide": "ee"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "おお",
            "rightSide": "oo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f0fb8ecb-3c5a-48de-99b7-032f7ac3ca43"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "aa",
            "rightSide": "ああ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ii",
            "rightSide": "いい"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "uu",
            "rightSide": "うう"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ee",
            "rightSide": "ええ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "oo",
            "rightSide": "おお"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "aa",
            "rightSide": "ああ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ii",
            "rightSide": "いい"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "uu",
            "rightSide": "うう"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ee",
            "rightSide": "ええ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "oo",
            "rightSide": "おお"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "68a24942-d0ae-49a5-8f96-992a328ea584"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ああ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "170d6624-33d5-4ce7-be79-d34fb7a6b6e0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b04669a9-3056-4d64-9b17-fe97d8375a20"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ううん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9e625802-4696-446b-8506-2d20c4883f54"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ええ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8e740071-2540-453a-b254-2f795e1c7dcc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おお",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "91a32d73-f24c-49e7-b29c-a5e80103b232"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おおきい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "き",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0bb39758-18eb-4a31-aaee-06638e8d69cd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ああそう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "あ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "そ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "88bdd8bd-7fd3-4c2e-8fa9-4725fada3548"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ええと",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "え",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9d3e89ae-9c4b-4445-ba54-8c4b2bd2d3f0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "いいね",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ね",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "161c83c1-a42d-4cdd-8f54-5377391f82ab"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おおぜい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ぜ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ああ", "いい", "うう", "ええ", "おお"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "458c7e4c-e0ff-47fd-9ae3-0918fd5d6eb8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ei",
        "options": ["ei", "ou"],
        "question": "えい"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "55d688e7-cd38-49be-8441-0f634d857ce3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ou",
        "options": ["ei", "ou"],
        "question": "おう"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dfbaad1c-db01-48e8-af83-38aa1b1d2d8b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "えい",
        "options": ["えい", "おう"],
        "question": "ei"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9261d883-b09a-40f4-90e7-8e5f709b4872"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おう",
        "options": ["えい", "おう"],
        "question": "ou"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "045f679c-0dbf-44e6-9837-eb9e5c2b9b82"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "えい",
        "options": ["えい", "おう"],
        "question": "えい"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e4e69d79-c3d2-45b9-bef3-f0dcfa9b9086"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おう",
        "options": ["えい", "おう"],
        "question": "おう"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6838f8fb-534b-4e44-a13d-741cf119330a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "えい",
            "rightSide": "ei"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "おう",
            "rightSide": "ou"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "えい",
            "rightSide": "ei"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "おう",
            "rightSide": "ou"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "256273d2-ce66-4e7d-b260-4cf9364215ea"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ei",
            "rightSide": "えい"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ou",
            "rightSide": "おう"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ei",
            "rightSide": "えい"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ou",
            "rightSide": "おう"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1f11c41d-7566-4334-8f87-0869e1dffb7e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "せんせい",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "せ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "せ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8ea067c4-f028-4c6b-a799-a5d94df7a0bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "こうこう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "こ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c5c54237-9e1e-4f1d-a836-121057cd4cae"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "けいさつ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "け",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "い",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "つ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9c29adba-7d47-449d-93a2-0e0f8461655f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "おとうさん",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "お",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "と",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "さ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ん",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "50cfb403-4de7-428b-8d71-de0abd64b556"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ほうほう",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ほ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ほ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "う",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["えい", "おう"],
      "letterType": "hiragana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d38c6c2d-c828-4541-be54-dcfadb65138c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "a",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "ア"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "965b2111-8837-4af8-a4ed-21adbb4699b1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "i",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "イ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "df5be015-98d7-4caa-8031-8a72158d792a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "u",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "ウ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "95f2ec8f-b353-4dd7-a5bd-4c5f96470ec8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "e",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "エ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9e519a58-23bb-48e7-ae9a-ec4d7e8131f9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "o",
        "options": ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"],
        "question": "オ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3d81a3e5-5ac6-4f93-868e-54cb3a2a4e82"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ア",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "a"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "06283a9a-0796-4a09-92fb-3601fc3a2520"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "イ",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "i"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c628bc5a-30f4-4ec3-b70c-bfcee915218a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ウ",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "u"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "34ee2c9d-1048-4061-a61f-3b434e5976ab"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エ",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "e"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f391877a-b826-40f1-881f-c5ffe4f24a82"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オ",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "o"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c16b26a0-0eca-4e86-9712-b86a8948871a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ア",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "ア"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e83a046e-5e6d-4914-b954-46c36d8a6f2f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "イ",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "イ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ca08184d-a969-4c1c-b776-727ca547e212"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ウ",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "ウ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fbe588b8-1c52-4d2b-992d-c57419a437b2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エ",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "エ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b0b807ba-7555-4025-81b3-7ea6d823d5c0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オ",
        "options": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
        "question": "オ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6890cc23-e60e-4d18-8829-94ff22ef91c3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ア",
            "rightSide": "a"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "イ",
            "rightSide": "i"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ウ",
            "rightSide": "u"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "エ",
            "rightSide": "e"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "オ",
            "rightSide": "o"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ア",
            "rightSide": "a"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "イ",
            "rightSide": "i"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ウ",
            "rightSide": "u"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "エ",
            "rightSide": "e"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "オ",
            "rightSide": "o"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "740da0f5-5754-4caf-868a-c06a563f34ae"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "a",
            "rightSide": "ア"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "i",
            "rightSide": "イ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "u",
            "rightSide": "ウ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "e",
            "rightSide": "エ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "o",
            "rightSide": "オ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "a",
            "rightSide": "ア"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "i",
            "rightSide": "イ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "u",
            "rightSide": "ウ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "e",
            "rightSide": "エ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "o",
            "rightSide": "オ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "32c847ec-8896-4584-8f8b-ec66a83d60f9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アイ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c865cba7-cb6f-4856-bf69-babcfb0456a1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "イオ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a74a05c9-1e76-4244-9032-8cb308080379"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アイウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "123ae919-d0a9-46d3-8020-f1dc8de00f17"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ウオ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7c92c2bf-acd4-4529-b21e-d22f1deda2b7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e24a2746-a27f-4f11-8fe4-19e62d24f1a7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エオ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f43919fc-60ba-47c3-8a6b-184f35cd9834"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アオ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "553a3444-be0a-4ab5-b828-057aa3194c6d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "イエ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ", "オ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ad4dd1d1-6a92-4ae8-9886-e6d98b266f89"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ka",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "カ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8dd5c71a-86ee-4989-bf3b-658cfab44136"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ki",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "キ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a28c09d4-e27c-422c-a7d7-4561d475d86d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ku",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "ク"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d4b93137-5766-4336-9a1a-847490ea0a90"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ke",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "ケ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4ac50579-6859-44e5-a178-8ff97a81c023"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ko",
        "options": ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke", "ko"],
        "question": "コ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cb88e364-2550-4e28-b277-7a4fc5ec4785"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カ",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "ka"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cad2f848-84ab-41f4-9d69-b29af3905691"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キ",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "ki"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9f8794ef-3f92-4320-86f4-dcb54b376c00"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ク",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "ku"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0917df67-7888-47a5-b762-a5903a0bdef1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ケ",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "ke"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6dbc6a05-3401-40b9-a5e4-2c61a9c79ed1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "コ",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "ko"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4bf79e76-d0d0-400a-9eb9-24512a537e68"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カ",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "カ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "33b3de1f-4888-4a7e-b43a-ec44ff97e878"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キ",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "キ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8abe60ba-97ee-4696-a080-9dd0af4b005f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ク",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "ク"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "07a2bef8-004a-4184-af5c-04b0389fd4b8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ケ",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "ケ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6800a266-d927-4730-a3af-bfdee356a18d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "コ",
        "options": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
        "question": "コ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cbe1e272-8e41-4f9c-bd99-59cf7e118bed"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "カ",
            "rightSide": "ka"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "キ",
            "rightSide": "ki"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ク",
            "rightSide": "ku"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ケ",
            "rightSide": "ke"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "コ",
            "rightSide": "ko"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "カ",
            "rightSide": "ka"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "キ",
            "rightSide": "ki"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ク",
            "rightSide": "ku"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ケ",
            "rightSide": "ke"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "コ",
            "rightSide": "ko"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c677684d-b89f-44a4-811b-bd007423bc94"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ka",
            "rightSide": "カ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ki",
            "rightSide": "キ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ku",
            "rightSide": "ク"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ke",
            "rightSide": "ケ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ko",
            "rightSide": "コ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ka",
            "rightSide": "カ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ki",
            "rightSide": "キ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ku",
            "rightSide": "ク"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ke",
            "rightSide": "ケ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ko",
            "rightSide": "コ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8411a727-3fea-4d04-a90c-da7c82d4714d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カキ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5064164a-3f8f-4a39-af3c-146160db7c6c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8871111c-d383-4f49-93f7-097d9ef41599"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "コエ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ee9ef70c-3245-4f07-96fb-c2469fd6d0e9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d3dc0690-dd0c-4c08-8241-c5764a1e6b04"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ケイ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ケ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "44f958b2-885c-4b3d-94bb-45e59a07b3e0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "クキ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4374af92-e61b-4744-80aa-da49707ea222"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オキ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "374f59dd-3b92-4813-8a83-a81f24ac4653"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アカ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fbaeaa35-a782-4f2e-a032-97e36e551d3b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "イコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0e7ac789-6eb8-4b32-8d04-87f98694b289"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ウケ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ケ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ", "コ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5d474fce-b4b1-4ecc-b8b6-05716035f655"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "sa",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "サ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "20989d6c-3a75-45b6-a231-258ad055d6d5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "shi",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "シ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "49106ed1-7b0a-49ca-9103-d8d200a26a0b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "su",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "ス"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1b0b4b5a-7b96-426a-b5d7-4d541b969dcb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "se",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "セ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "41f38efa-3cd9-4792-9c39-b1b535e2969d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "so",
        "options": ["sa", "shi", "su", "se", "so"],
        "question": "ソ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "455da552-5f72-44f2-af89-da78ae26bd9c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "サ",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "sa"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7321cbfc-8d63-4a52-9927-1daad22db16d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シ",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "shi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "63ba404a-e539-4d02-b4fd-ec1c93b4561b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ス",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "su"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "71e06dcb-314a-4058-a6c3-50428410417b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "セ",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "se"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "19151080-5884-4f26-a566-ebe217b22326"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ソ",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "so"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1ec5cb12-e077-430b-b201-e42e34df8cd8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "サ",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "サ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a7594057-0f03-4a40-868a-eab379c5aa99"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シ",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "シ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "083f3590-3442-4abe-8f85-5f4523fa35b2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ス",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "ス"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ee5a3b9a-dd70-4557-a0f4-bf567444d142"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "セ",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "セ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "71bb9581-78d4-48b8-92d7-8e241ab94b5a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ソ",
        "options": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
        "question": "ソ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "add85b73-59ee-4dba-a7d0-eec837e84300"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "サ",
            "rightSide": "sa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "シ",
            "rightSide": "shi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ス",
            "rightSide": "su"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "セ",
            "rightSide": "se"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ソ",
            "rightSide": "so"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "サ",
            "rightSide": "sa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "シ",
            "rightSide": "shi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ス",
            "rightSide": "su"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "セ",
            "rightSide": "se"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ソ",
            "rightSide": "so"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5caafa12-bf5e-40ed-906f-236365c806e4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "sa",
            "rightSide": "サ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "shi",
            "rightSide": "シ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "su",
            "rightSide": "ス"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "se",
            "rightSide": "セ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "so",
            "rightSide": "ソ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "sa",
            "rightSide": "サ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "shi",
            "rightSide": "シ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "su",
            "rightSide": "ス"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "se",
            "rightSide": "セ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "so",
            "rightSide": "ソ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "55e38c8a-20ce-41f6-9c04-d7fe7a29878e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "スシ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8ddf9aef-49c7-42b6-ba69-8766143c7abb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "サカ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "サ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b0c8be74-9210-4738-81b9-1e2c60156a73"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ソコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ソ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d6eac9e0-5fdb-4f44-b95e-6b76e53d0f2c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シオ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9ea6cebb-62ee-4a56-91ad-2bc6ac601348"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "セカイ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "セ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f794a34c-fbed-4d30-91a1-164c52428260"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カサ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "サ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6b1d04cb-340c-427c-94dc-b50508963c25"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "スコア",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "35e5385c-7f5c-4dee-8b3a-dbdde25fd04c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キソ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ソ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "519ecaf1-33b6-4d48-9aab-1a21ff5fb402"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シカ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cc7531ce-41eb-4e7a-850d-76f9f1d07e77"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アシ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ", "ソ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "03eb8312-d414-4966-ba64-9897838a7205"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ta",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "タ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7624fbf3-a0cc-4eab-8d07-8d9784ee46da"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "chi",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "チ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "58c0c8c5-fbe5-4db8-bea3-b76684303194"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "tsu",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "ツ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "55b08405-d36e-407d-ac0b-ea3db2107351"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "te",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "テ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2b97d727-854b-4ecc-aef1-5635cad5babe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "to",
        "options": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te", "to"],
        "question": "ト"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1b601d3e-369f-487f-b4ed-ddbf6b7732fc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "タ",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "ta"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4d3ee3be-7be1-4a01-bf63-4f4cc028336f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チ",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "chi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f92bfe87-01f0-40bf-ae07-02e7c996098f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ツ",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "tsu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ae361283-63c2-42fe-a3e0-1f3356694a30"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "テ",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "te"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0ef86426-3088-40fd-9e16-e5f8b752dab7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ト",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "to"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ded35103-8bc9-45e3-82ce-02221641a289"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "タ",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "タ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d9f7023a-4b39-4d92-a1c5-cc47d2f262eb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チ",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "チ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1fadd2da-1069-4c52-8040-caa477bb9df0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ツ",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "ツ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8f0f85bd-9712-4280-9c0b-31b1b7db01dc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "テ",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "テ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "10392907-1a51-4341-9798-419de76a17ee"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ト",
        "options": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
        "question": "ト"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f091256e-4b0e-42ef-8a56-49c74fba8395"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "タ",
            "rightSide": "ta"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "チ",
            "rightSide": "chi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ツ",
            "rightSide": "tsu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "テ",
            "rightSide": "te"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ト",
            "rightSide": "to"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "タ",
            "rightSide": "ta"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "チ",
            "rightSide": "chi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ツ",
            "rightSide": "tsu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "テ",
            "rightSide": "te"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ト",
            "rightSide": "to"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b732122d-a011-4813-bbbf-7c43cd85d2f8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ta",
            "rightSide": "タ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "chi",
            "rightSide": "チ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "tsu",
            "rightSide": "ツ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "te",
            "rightSide": "テ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "to",
            "rightSide": "ト"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ta",
            "rightSide": "タ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "chi",
            "rightSide": "チ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "tsu",
            "rightSide": "ツ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "te",
            "rightSide": "テ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "to",
            "rightSide": "ト"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4e252128-3395-49e7-9825-72c4404653ea"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "タコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "タ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ed92c740-43c9-431f-a34a-473bcdadaeb8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チカ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4e517291-3401-4b04-b827-7beb2f79aff0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ツキ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ツ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e490b2dd-3fbc-4df0-8b22-aaf5408891fc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "テキ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "テ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0237c742-21de-4ac9-b8d8-61943843ef98"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "トキ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fa57b846-fda5-4605-990b-c6a21ffca487"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カタ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "タ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a0caeb40-8ac0-4d98-adba-5e140b52a57e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "トコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "68703b57-7e2f-4d69-9255-3947d3386db9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チサ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "サ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c250a118-a3a8-4a8b-a5c3-649a1245bbde"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アチ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dfcba2b5-ffaf-43eb-8571-472c4832090a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エツ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ツ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ", "ト"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4002d5e3-191e-4a71-97e2-609bd089dded"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "na",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "ナ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e0627ea6-a758-430c-ae6a-b35c0712a9f9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ni",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "ニ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fedf9238-3e16-4d11-bb87-18669973ad1a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "nu",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "ヌ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "67a84ce3-9397-4838-b139-1251aff7a5bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ne",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "ネ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "191c3603-a4b1-47cd-8f5e-cba69c9b0208"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "no",
        "options": ["na", "ni", "nu", "ne", "no"],
        "question": "ノ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "04ea2547-2019-40e0-8be4-172e600a7806"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ナ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "na"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3ae289dc-08ca-49ba-9fca-82200ba3df7c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "ni"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6c5a7b3e-eead-4522-8241-aad5dfe4bfcd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヌ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "nu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a37551a5-77de-45be-94f6-02bb9398a149"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ネ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "ne"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9597688e-d3cc-48ca-a192-3f7403885cb8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ノ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "no"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "00fc9bf8-d722-4884-9ab4-5d9356dc1728"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ナ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "ナ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e331c186-3b43-4333-9966-441d77a8c08a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "ニ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ad9e0b7e-12b6-4a95-b1dc-4dabf6241fe3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヌ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "ヌ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "03cf418d-4891-4924-bb47-fbcc0d1cea96"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ネ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "ネ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b41581ba-736a-4e5f-b817-10c186b1b6bf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ノ",
        "options": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
        "question": "ノ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c975af83-1784-403d-b9b6-a367591cec7f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ナ",
            "rightSide": "na"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ニ",
            "rightSide": "ni"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヌ",
            "rightSide": "nu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ネ",
            "rightSide": "ne"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ノ",
            "rightSide": "no"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ナ",
            "rightSide": "na"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ニ",
            "rightSide": "ni"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヌ",
            "rightSide": "nu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ネ",
            "rightSide": "ne"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ノ",
            "rightSide": "no"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d45cf3ee-eb02-48a6-a2f7-2787115b704d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "na",
            "rightSide": "ナ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ni",
            "rightSide": "ニ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nu",
            "rightSide": "ヌ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ne",
            "rightSide": "ネ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "no",
            "rightSide": "ノ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "na",
            "rightSide": "ナ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ni",
            "rightSide": "ニ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nu",
            "rightSide": "ヌ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ne",
            "rightSide": "ネ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "no",
            "rightSide": "ノ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "accb8537-3e0c-478f-8354-bc289ce59f41"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ナイ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ナ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fb4b32e2-96ad-4bb5-b609-d896357c6c5f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ab6c0a20-aae8-426c-872b-a0d00a61ffa8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ノコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ノ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9f09550c-a3b8-4d8c-91fc-c4a2ba6e5ce0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ネコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ネ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3d3d8ad7-6bf7-484e-8c05-477ccf81e00d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヌク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヌ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6120d0cc-8c10-487a-b712-051319f0b84f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "タニ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "タ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "62bf615e-4f18-4c4e-b4fb-b606243ae787"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カネ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ネ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "646e2152-de20-4919-9781-b254d00cb79b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ネタ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ネ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "タ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a7401a58-ddb0-439c-bd0f-e19bd54a6f6e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "コネ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ネ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "64a9c402-614b-4791-b39a-be7bdb2863c0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アニ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ", "ノ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9b98f2a0-0c40-44f6-9783-c52823322a60"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ha",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "ハ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "371fbf63-924b-42cc-a5f2-864bb262edf3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "hi",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "ヒ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "75aaa6a0-ccdb-49b9-901a-cc35da3f18b8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "fu",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "フ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "db30f30b-4564-4739-9015-90f3edbb2b5f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "he",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "ヘ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "74f32c9e-eee1-41f3-acf0-eb9bb7f2aefe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ho",
        "options": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he", "ho"],
        "question": "ホ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a35621b1-4968-4786-b26e-28e0ebf0c239"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ハ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "ha"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a04653eb-43c6-4b4b-9cf8-e3eedbdff390"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "hi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "78330e60-fb3c-4b22-99e2-4c611fcd7523"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "フ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "fu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2c62c845-b514-4c6a-8245-9e1a3810dfb2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヘ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "he"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "219a4529-74ae-437a-b931-1f762bc064b0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ホ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "ho"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "21e69330-c971-412f-9f2a-b759c06fa908"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ハ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "ハ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0d672636-3e71-4e38-a3e5-9e7feb9f7a42"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "ヒ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8230a9c6-a711-46e8-9247-d27e02cc4003"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "フ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "フ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "36499489-c14c-479c-8d20-18cf746fa322"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヘ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "ヘ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "de38c9f3-21c7-4fd3-877d-da64f839cc71"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ホ",
        "options": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
        "question": "ホ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7d066d01-54d5-45a9-967c-96c3032e9da5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ハ",
            "rightSide": "ha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヒ",
            "rightSide": "hi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "フ",
            "rightSide": "fu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヘ",
            "rightSide": "he"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ホ",
            "rightSide": "ho"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ハ",
            "rightSide": "ha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヒ",
            "rightSide": "hi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "フ",
            "rightSide": "fu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヘ",
            "rightSide": "he"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ホ",
            "rightSide": "ho"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "aed14e50-cf13-4bba-a294-f7e556e5931c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "モ",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "モ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c06e6d2b-4c7e-4328-91ef-86b34cb67e9d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ha",
            "rightSide": "ハ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hi",
            "rightSide": "ヒ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "fu",
            "rightSide": "フ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "he",
            "rightSide": "ヘ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ho",
            "rightSide": "ホ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ha",
            "rightSide": "ハ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hi",
            "rightSide": "ヒ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "fu",
            "rightSide": "フ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "he",
            "rightSide": "ヘ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ho",
            "rightSide": "ホ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0fc24234-0d85-419e-80b4-29f9c2fdafed"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ホシ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ホ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "194d61b2-e42e-46f0-ba1d-6f691ba5a473"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ハコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ハ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5361e701-169b-41da-aa98-b6bed44bc4c5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "フネ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "フ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ネ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5656a52b-591a-449f-9dcb-682513de1bc2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒト",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヒ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ab58becc-6e38-4d4a-8d69-44ebc0636c83"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヘタ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヘ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "タ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ec87d982-8ffd-473f-8ea3-26bb4cfc3ff3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カホ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ホ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0f925ad9-84ad-4a89-93d6-7164796e2a30"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ホネ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ホ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ネ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "244cb7f7-0d4c-4965-8c7b-74530be2773c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アフ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "フ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0d24f2bf-aa58-4fb7-980a-0fc96327d5f8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ハナ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ハ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ナ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "00ce2b42-292d-4fe7-b748-c6629b2400e0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ネフ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ネ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "フ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ", "ホ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ad5c95b7-fb0b-4229-9696-860fd956cfb6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ma",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "マ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "861880cf-8484-421c-a96c-0dda17906bf5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "mi",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "ミ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "68e3ca63-5240-406f-b9b5-edb29f1bf83d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "mu",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "ム"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5fa3262f-da7a-4c47-8012-24bc9eace2ec"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "me",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "メ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "533370fd-8e66-4e4f-83fb-c99fc4ad0f98"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "mo",
        "options": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me", "mo"],
        "question": "モ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4b87e9eb-3918-4d75-aaad-d28c6663b818"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "マ",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "ma"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b5ff9b53-9ffe-40eb-9855-37cba2033225"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミ",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "mi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "00f879ba-990d-44ee-937c-cc96de8e5df8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ム",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "mu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "30490242-3176-43b4-ba42-749ff24bf4b5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "メ",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "me"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a95a8784-e2cf-4d48-a5df-6c5d8e2c5c8d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "モ",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "mo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3791b60c-15b4-4117-a14e-71dca6dad756"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "マ",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "マ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4928c7f3-e406-465f-a744-6500419a150a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミ",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "ミ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "45e52de7-fbab-46d6-bbc3-c0cc776c457e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ム",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "ム"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "56096457-b2d8-482c-bde1-3eaf7c60bd65"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "メ",
        "options": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
        "question": "メ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e95faed8-9107-451c-9112-b6891cbe503f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "マ",
            "rightSide": "ma"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ミ",
            "rightSide": "mi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ム",
            "rightSide": "mu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "メ",
            "rightSide": "me"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "モ",
            "rightSide": "mo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "マ",
            "rightSide": "ma"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ミ",
            "rightSide": "mi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ム",
            "rightSide": "mu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "メ",
            "rightSide": "me"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "モ",
            "rightSide": "mo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a96c1ce7-b5bc-4988-85f2-db4616fad963"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ma",
            "rightSide": "マ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mi",
            "rightSide": "ミ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mu",
            "rightSide": "ム"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "me",
            "rightSide": "メ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mo",
            "rightSide": "モ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ma",
            "rightSide": "マ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mi",
            "rightSide": "ミ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mu",
            "rightSide": "ム"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "me",
            "rightSide": "メ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "mo",
            "rightSide": "モ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5847f665-cab0-4de4-b28b-7669d5b047db"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "マチ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "マ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "523aa246-52e1-48c9-b0a3-c9cd5ed0d25a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "モノ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "モ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ノ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f9b9d719-3dc6-4889-b13c-8d446979f3e9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミカ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7fb49792-5db1-4854-8fd8-6f5309480aae"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "メモ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "メ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "モ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2828a211-0d9a-4b28-afd3-9dbc0b576066"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ムネ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ム",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ネ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5864abfc-4ace-43c0-ab40-0e7adec8439b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カモ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "モ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "27966957-594d-414e-ba87-589a435ce9ff"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "サム",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "サ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ム",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "eeb1fd3c-8770-4328-b60e-826155008c38"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "トモ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "モ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f645f4f1-4642-4040-99b1-bd8aaca27839"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アミ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "faacf09b-4322-4849-a47a-f89f701b6180"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ナマ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ナ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "マ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ", "モ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4b90fda0-75f5-4f35-93ec-91e17b5e0f7f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ya",
        "options": ["ya", "yu", "yo"],
        "question": "ヤ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "363bbce7-9f54-43a2-97b0-20a870d5c953"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "yu",
        "options": ["ya", "yu", "yo"],
        "question": "ユ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "77921248-2e7c-4591-b010-8c1a335e2d14"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "yo",
        "options": ["ya", "yu", "yo"],
        "question": "ヨ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a5493c2c-dabc-4782-8691-b899f7075708"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヤ",
        "options": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
        "question": "ya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4e6e99b8-2f81-4680-942d-46ef8d51948f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ユ",
        "options": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
        "question": "yu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "09b0ca33-aedd-4a4b-8c63-5682ee408fe2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヨ",
        "options": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
        "question": "yo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "40086cdd-ba3b-4df6-9ebd-2488082a9422"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヤ",
        "options": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
        "question": "ヤ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f1d9c366-66bc-4561-be79-39cc431b457c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ユ",
        "options": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
        "question": "ユ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c5acb642-7610-4db7-998a-a0526e66b042"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヨ",
        "options": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
        "question": "ヨ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0d3cd9b6-0e28-4b12-8448-a05eab3271bf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ヤ",
            "rightSide": "ya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ユ",
            "rightSide": "yu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヨ",
            "rightSide": "yo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ヤ",
            "rightSide": "ya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ユ",
            "rightSide": "yu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヨ",
            "rightSide": "yo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "aaf76ce5-de4f-46a1-aeaf-5b11a6b0b85d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ロ",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "ロ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1a4c8118-6ce0-4a22-82f5-dba1595f703c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ya",
            "rightSide": "ヤ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "yu",
            "rightSide": "ユ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "yo",
            "rightSide": "ヨ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ya",
            "rightSide": "ヤ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "yu",
            "rightSide": "ユ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "yo",
            "rightSide": "ヨ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8b457b88-9b51-435c-aeb5-1118b5f8aa3d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヤミ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヤ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b8c91e3f-997d-40e6-bd6a-182c4fce3937"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ユメ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ユ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "メ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "88d05b2f-7bf2-41a9-873e-bb63dc5788eb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヨコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヨ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b0351fce-df2b-4321-87c0-cf97e4d39cde"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カユイ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ユ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b06ce676-0f89-41dc-a7f9-f2b9558cc286"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヤマ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヤ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "マ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5588cd91-56eb-43f7-b6c3-986e6ce19ef6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ユウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ユ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "de7574e0-ada2-47bd-b984-293b8aec32aa"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヨミ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヨ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3493bc40-c9a6-4ee5-b8f8-1ef06947e31f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "タユミ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "タ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ユ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "26944d63-2bdc-4c78-9867-cac1e1ed5f85"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ユナ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ユ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ナ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3db47dce-f369-45a9-8901-544799f197fe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "モユル",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "モ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ユ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ル",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d6073b96-3bc9-4766-91c0-0ace5701c970"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ra",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "ラ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f37be391-e402-4019-9c7b-d839d71bd037"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ri",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "リ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "24fa9cb3-6acb-499f-806b-79996cf22011"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ru",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "ル"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9129c137-ae9c-47ad-9e42-259f91105303"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "re",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "レ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8ed4fcf3-1b83-40b2-80dd-3eaffdcfe3ad"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ro",
        "options": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re", "ro"],
        "question": "ロ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "56a518a1-259c-42c2-bf1f-3972514137dc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ラ",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "ra"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "78b45ed2-b9c0-48d4-9de8-2fc0be1e8589"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リ",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "ri"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "91bc4e9f-3d91-4834-bd68-064ac5bc1493"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ル",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "ru"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5462b55f-c37b-4386-b518-ea5c48388c82"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "レ",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "re"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "03a09286-c6bb-4a0a-ae0a-89181c5b1278"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ロ",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "ro"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8156b829-4807-4e18-be8a-830abc659e19"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ラ",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "ラ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3f5a9c3a-8a9c-45f7-96a0-4aff0fdc6492"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リ",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "リ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d38955e3-2835-457a-bfb3-a4b5f0a377ba"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ル",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "ル"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "81a7d998-2909-454c-b1e5-0e5ecd522f8c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "レ",
        "options": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
        "question": "レ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2374272e-2508-4369-93a4-284011f45f17"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ラ",
            "rightSide": "ra"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "リ",
            "rightSide": "ri"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ル",
            "rightSide": "ru"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "レ",
            "rightSide": "re"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ロ",
            "rightSide": "ro"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ラ",
            "rightSide": "ra"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "リ",
            "rightSide": "ri"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ル",
            "rightSide": "ru"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "レ",
            "rightSide": "re"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ロ",
            "rightSide": "ro"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "728563b5-e2a3-4eaa-a449-5784ea0fb3e6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ra",
            "rightSide": "ラ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ri",
            "rightSide": "リ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ru",
            "rightSide": "ル"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "re",
            "rightSide": "レ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ro",
            "rightSide": "ロ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ra",
            "rightSide": "ラ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ri",
            "rightSide": "リ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ru",
            "rightSide": "ル"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "re",
            "rightSide": "レ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ro",
            "rightSide": "ロ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "df46fba3-9350-43a2-9b75-97360dc79ea4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ラメ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ラ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "メ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ec8d6fcc-feab-47ab-b3a3-fc80bc6b01c4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リボン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ボ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5db03b2a-005d-4222-a83c-86eca7061623"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ルミ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ル",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9f33b5e5-4688-400f-b812-7ec7e6d9bd83"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "レモン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "レ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "モ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c79f7bfd-70cd-458e-a43b-1c5e6fb9451f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ロク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ロ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f7abe0d3-83fc-46c7-b953-c5de7e05f8b0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カリ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3b2e1054-0e46-43f2-be80-7f39a61b5a98"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ソラ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ソ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ラ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1d66bd0e-4d2f-415c-915d-8333d10739f2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "トラ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ラ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7cdbab8e-a7d9-4fdc-9b8a-92b16a08b670"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "68e6f65c-cdbd-4c52-96a9-c22a70582ab1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "メロ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "メ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ロ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ", "ロ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bc1d8eb1-449f-4891-a980-061d04ebfb89"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "wa",
        "options": ["wa", "wo"],
        "question": "ワ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e3acf4be-fefa-4ccb-8e7b-bff0432e7323"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "wo",
        "options": ["wa", "wo"],
        "question": "ヲ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "abd75060-9e3d-4c10-b185-c7a241f8bea6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ワ",
        "options": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
        "question": "wa"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a393a72d-54bf-4d10-86da-6b6a1e6c0b41"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヲ",
        "options": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
        "question": "wo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bc4800b6-250c-45a8-bcfc-054a8e6d4f1c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ワ",
        "options": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
        "question": "ワ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "63c459f0-1d8d-4b1e-85fa-85fd6df71b4d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヲ",
        "options": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
        "question": "ヲ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "81f25cbe-86d6-425c-b0ea-9f3e09b2fb79"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ワ",
            "rightSide": "wa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヲ",
            "rightSide": "wo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ワ",
            "rightSide": "wa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヲ",
            "rightSide": "wo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9d0304d1-a0ea-48a8-831f-8079b35ea6fb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "wa",
            "rightSide": "ワ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "wo",
            "rightSide": "ヲ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "wa",
            "rightSide": "ワ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "wo",
            "rightSide": "ヲ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e59973d5-1fae-4ae4-bc99-b60431518e1c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ワカメ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ワ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "メ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "01d568a2-d7e1-4270-acd0-b9645bb4ca16"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ワサビ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ワ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "サ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ビ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "81e09a0f-f592-4216-b2e4-0cc8a82bcb61"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ワラ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ワ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ラ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "292e8539-f4cc-4bd1-8c6c-915cc110080a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ワン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ワ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "36aea90a-998e-41fa-8756-dfc4e2b0d1c1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ワカイ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ワ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ワ", "ヲ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "db15f9c2-53d2-4cbe-9d7c-f59651fa9514"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "n",
        "options": ["n"],
        "question": "ン"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b273d554-7b89-48d9-965e-716a156fa21e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ン",
        "options": ["ン"],
        "question": "n"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0107a49b-856d-416b-8ff0-7b01e5a94b33"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ン",
        "options": ["ン"],
        "question": "ン"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "afea7f7c-b4e4-4c35-8526-e47d24507ead"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ン",
            "rightSide": "n"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ン",
            "rightSide": "n"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dbeea1a9-e65d-4473-9e97-0b3dae6316f0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "n",
            "rightSide": "ン"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "n",
            "rightSide": "ン"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b4371525-be2c-4307-889b-3a9b4abddeda"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8399796a-565f-4e4b-8066-4b0423afb2e8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "コン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "25fbc6ad-2e21-40bd-8871-a25a83c9279a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "テン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "テ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ce608089-3e9c-4054-8050-64cbe04ed061"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "サン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "サ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e3c90b2b-406a-4074-bec1-d053b366d06a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ン"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3ebdbea0-fe4c-41b9-9284-db754feb6964"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ga",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "ガ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "07143c62-d551-41c1-8d16-37909b6f9fa9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gi",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "ギ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "923288e7-09e5-414a-9c3a-24b7092f79ef"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gu",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "グ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6093334d-c7b6-4f9a-a08e-3a3b952955a8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ge",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "ゲ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "afa1b670-5d15-4a97-a6c4-80a391742d49"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "go",
        "options": ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        "question": "ゴ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9ff714ea-c49b-41cb-84f3-773711cb63b2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ガ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "ga"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ec30f2f5-b4a9-4945-91a9-58f465021da8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "gi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "45c06731-6ec2-4656-b158-10f50dca9e1f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "グ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "gu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c2dcc91e-1de8-4179-ac77-956281e180c9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゲ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "ge"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "48c0cbee-b66b-40a1-971f-8111ccaefa48"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゴ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "go"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fd27d181-f39a-487f-81da-bd8755cd1d7b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ガ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "ガ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "78f021c3-63c1-436f-a503-11b1a1ed3cda"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "ギ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4aa95c00-4fd4-4173-bc12-520e478c646d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "グ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "グ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3ce333f8-1fd0-4c0f-a0d1-1628a3391015"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゲ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "ゲ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c444d8fc-0086-4fa0-97eb-85c980388617"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゴ",
        "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
        "question": "ゴ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f3465b1c-5e95-4887-a640-e7043932dd48"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ガ",
            "rightSide": "ga"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ギ",
            "rightSide": "gi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "グ",
            "rightSide": "gu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゲ",
            "rightSide": "ge"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゴ",
            "rightSide": "go"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ガ",
            "rightSide": "ga"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ギ",
            "rightSide": "gi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "グ",
            "rightSide": "gu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゲ",
            "rightSide": "ge"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゴ",
            "rightSide": "go"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2026067e-6fca-46b6-a01c-9402084f1ae9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ga",
            "rightSide": "ガ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gi",
            "rightSide": "ギ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gu",
            "rightSide": "グ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ge",
            "rightSide": "ゲ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "go",
            "rightSide": "ゴ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ga",
            "rightSide": "ガ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gi",
            "rightSide": "ギ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gu",
            "rightSide": "グ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ge",
            "rightSide": "ゲ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "go",
            "rightSide": "ゴ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "33265fe3-c99a-4d3e-b856-429ec749a929"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ガク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ガ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ca008305-b34f-402e-8e99-a71877eb0954"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゴク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ゴ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "00f1d483-d5b8-45e6-82d3-4b0dce319509"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゲキ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ゲ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "09e41e03-e9c2-4eb9-a8e6-bc3cd34d5e81"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "グン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "グ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f7cffaae-91f9-4e80-aa21-f3febf3daad3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ギ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ガ", "ギ", "グ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "83c09e43-6657-4b08-9392-aac7be8d0cfb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "za",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "ザ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "453caed1-42d1-4188-9bc7-75b773327f6f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ji",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "ジ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b1c55521-86a3-4da9-bed2-98723d8c4f22"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "zu",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "ズ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c41c936e-e62c-4f15-9c76-7d4241bb0be6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ze",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "ゼ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9045a22a-7fd2-4f64-9c41-ffe3a712d94c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "zo",
        "options": ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        "question": "ゾ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "da110a84-01cb-41c5-976e-83bb7d851344"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ザ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "za"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "83ab3c7c-bc58-4ccb-ac34-fdf5d841f018"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "ji"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1aa43e2e-11f8-4e64-99a8-cde74714d6da"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ズ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "zu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "095e11c1-16cd-42a4-a062-8b3e57ce5068"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゼ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "ze"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e44a3424-d16e-4adb-b24f-a151f38475d6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゾ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "zo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e985df88-55a4-4cf6-9123-45be69369533"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ザ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "ザ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8b886ad0-e54b-4a14-ab75-e132a2f644a6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "ジ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "70cfc34c-9f25-41cc-84c1-c2fafba7caa6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ズ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "ズ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1807b13d-5bda-474b-bc49-f19aa7f21ed2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゼ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "ゼ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "05441cb7-208a-40a1-bd3c-cdb45e7c0a61"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゾ",
        "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
        "question": "ゾ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "928d84b0-c210-44fc-b18b-267561beecc2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gya",
        "options": ["gya", "gyu", "gyo"],
        "question": "ギャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e6f33539-b631-4b09-b578-126f1c3ead60"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ザ",
            "rightSide": "za"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ジ",
            "rightSide": "ji"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ズ",
            "rightSide": "zu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゼ",
            "rightSide": "ze"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゾ",
            "rightSide": "zo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ザ",
            "rightSide": "za"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ジ",
            "rightSide": "ji"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ズ",
            "rightSide": "zu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゼ",
            "rightSide": "ze"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ゾ",
            "rightSide": "zo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "14a936a2-bbc0-45d8-967b-9c261585d83a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "za",
            "rightSide": "ザ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ji",
            "rightSide": "ジ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zu",
            "rightSide": "ズ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ze",
            "rightSide": "ゼ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zo",
            "rightSide": "ゾ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "za",
            "rightSide": "ザ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ji",
            "rightSide": "ジ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zu",
            "rightSide": "ズ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ze",
            "rightSide": "ゼ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zo",
            "rightSide": "ゾ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ef449a2f-f63c-4cc7-b3e7-9eb00ad9fc56"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジゴク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ゴ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "45432939-5110-4611-b4f2-d865ff57ca09"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゾク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ゾ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "133250cc-cf88-4b17-9d1b-abd1aa253332"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ゲンジ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ゲ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "34593b0c-3c94-4158-9958-31693ccd5be4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "セイゾン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "セ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ゾ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "68196cf3-fd1d-43dd-b411-4b74bba0998a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゼ", "ゾ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6a6501f6-7885-4ff7-a797-883eb87951a3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "da",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "ダ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b9d126e6-0c7e-4ad4-9b7e-aeb02095ff35"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ji",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "ヂ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "13ecf359-c5fa-4ef9-961b-d60f063db223"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "zu",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "ヅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c30d590a-864f-4c61-8576-e96bbdb095cd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "de",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "デ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3645a74e-4dbd-4af2-96d9-0c350ce46d2a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "do",
        "options": ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        "question": "ド"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f5bc2ee9-0765-4e58-b886-6f01a6593a37"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ダ",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "da"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "74157f80-1da9-4624-803d-90878153ca1c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヂ",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "ji"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cbeed445-2a0f-4ae1-a633-0dddf53e1a34"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヅ",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "zu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "45df0a9c-8054-44b6-a16d-19df662a8a31"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "デ",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "de"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "aa347944-a3d1-4595-aed1-668bc1d3872d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ド",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "do"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bf813cd0-1ba9-4038-92b0-2a513b283252"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ダ",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "ダ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f627dfc7-054c-4df1-9755-a95c756f5784"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヂ",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "ヂ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "32d674bb-4984-4eff-a41d-194fe0f0edfb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヅ",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "ヅ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "77528440-1e6c-4ebd-aa58-b6724e80dd36"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "デ",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "デ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "755e2d06-c46d-4ccf-9f7e-2ef10af09b90"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ド",
        "options": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
        "question": "ド"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a7c5dd3a-c536-4bff-b88c-ccea40cc1119"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キュート",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "19ca4348-708c-4081-a285-8377ea51568f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ダ",
            "rightSide": "da"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヂ",
            "rightSide": "ji"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヅ",
            "rightSide": "zu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "デ",
            "rightSide": "de"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ド",
            "rightSide": "do"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ダ",
            "rightSide": "da"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヂ",
            "rightSide": "ji"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヅ",
            "rightSide": "zu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "デ",
            "rightSide": "de"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ド",
            "rightSide": "do"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dbe5c3e0-3647-43c3-b6aa-bf260cc716e6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "da",
            "rightSide": "ダ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ji",
            "rightSide": "ヂ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zu",
            "rightSide": "ヅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "de",
            "rightSide": "デ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "do",
            "rightSide": "ド"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "da",
            "rightSide": "ダ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ji",
            "rightSide": "ヂ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "zu",
            "rightSide": "ヅ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "de",
            "rightSide": "デ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "do",
            "rightSide": "ド"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ddc40918-5904-427e-ba77-c47b1d923259"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ドク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ド",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b0cfee7b-3445-4546-a151-a0b641138ddc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "デンワ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "デ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ワ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ef0c7d8a-c7fb-4134-aa9f-62b37cee3831"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ダンス",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ダ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f035f429-9141-4889-94ac-97f65e51fb6c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "デコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "デ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "55532d32-03a8-4fe6-87a7-9abc15199208"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ドア",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ド",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ダ", "ヂ", "ヅ", "デ", "ド"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b80a69f4-5a8f-42d0-9633-a344e675982e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ba",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "バ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ad7abbba-55a4-458e-b0d4-f5f942e7b18a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "bi",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "ビ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c1bbc403-0b0a-45a5-a000-f5fda89b6808"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "bu",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "ブ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "18b58165-f353-4ce5-848f-e8a40e21d33e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "be",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "ベ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "38691a15-69ae-4e3f-b44f-8b94435034a5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "bo",
        "options": ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        "question": "ボ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f8fcdec6-450f-4d4e-aea5-20bf2359ef38"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "バ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "ba"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "76580a46-f5c2-4356-8e75-f9963143dc65"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "bi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "99cd86bb-4187-4e73-b78b-71a35a89eb0e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ブ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "bu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3d6f7bc5-6e9d-4723-8867-7437548b6b6b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ベ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "be"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d9fc39e0-108d-48df-80b0-f5a62deb6eb8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ボ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "bo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ba38cf5a-2f02-4d76-a06c-a39eb6cd7871"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "バ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "バ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7519410e-e506-478c-b478-e66c25733966"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "ビ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "53b5457d-e270-4d6e-ac62-442f85570d9f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ブ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "ブ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a530aedb-1099-4b50-bea2-23d7861d774e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ベ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "ベ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7b077e71-13c7-4000-87ff-7f264ae68d4b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ボ",
        "options": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
        "question": "ボ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9ba1c6bc-1f10-4c84-bec5-1ec65a9f2568"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キョウリュウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "941ad9df-3ac3-4dcd-b824-067da3428f2a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "バ",
            "rightSide": "ba"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ビ",
            "rightSide": "bi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ブ",
            "rightSide": "bu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ベ",
            "rightSide": "be"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ボ",
            "rightSide": "bo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "バ",
            "rightSide": "ba"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ビ",
            "rightSide": "bi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ブ",
            "rightSide": "bu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ベ",
            "rightSide": "be"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ボ",
            "rightSide": "bo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "48fe95a5-891d-49fa-8b56-fd97daa593aa"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ba",
            "rightSide": "バ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bi",
            "rightSide": "ビ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bu",
            "rightSide": "ブ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "be",
            "rightSide": "ベ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bo",
            "rightSide": "ボ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ba",
            "rightSide": "バ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bi",
            "rightSide": "ビ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bu",
            "rightSide": "ブ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "be",
            "rightSide": "ベ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "bo",
            "rightSide": "ボ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d17a935d-dda1-4c95-bd93-721470ce0b77"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "バス",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "バ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e1cd3d84-56b3-4f30-b347-e28b7dc63f15"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ボタン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ボ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "タ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6ca1247d-107b-4622-8585-e1d5508c35ff"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ベッド",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ベ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ド",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "aeaf6b2c-5bd1-4160-97c5-4b8f800d2ac3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "バナナ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "バ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ナ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ナ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c46680cf-c681-4d20-abe4-3f37efeafdb1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ブタ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ブ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "タ",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["バ", "ビ", "ブ", "ベ", "ボ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8c3d84e3-5a51-431c-aadc-7492f5730678"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pa",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "パ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c9b24cf3-9b77-4118-b326-fa00df1204d2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pi",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "ピ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b78bba1a-0254-4bc3-b72d-d8a64ad7b791"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pu",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "プ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2d712f31-2f55-43f1-93f6-521a254c7518"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pe",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "ペ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bae20243-de0b-48ca-972e-d49e9204549d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "po",
        "options": ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        "question": "ポ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9c092dd8-588c-41ce-81b5-7b692799e1bd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "パ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "pa"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ea347cda-1a40-495b-8207-23ac653b747c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "pi"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a19eca88-f2c0-480f-b96e-3859e969715e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "プ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "pu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "485d09e1-20d9-4b7f-90a5-734b3eb10471"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ペ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "pe"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f2d7448c-edf2-4ced-9774-6ba987852da9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ポ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "po"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "afd2c4d9-49dd-419a-a5bc-9721bc83d98f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "パ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "パ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8f12dd98-e296-43ed-bf47-3f08c44824ce"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "ピ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a37726ff-a603-4a3c-b8fe-80b9613d7533"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "プ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "プ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d6ce7761-bbc7-4924-b18e-bd9031177e18"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ペ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "ペ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d372a791-33f3-4e61-bfff-94f2e4c46b2b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ポ",
        "options": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
        "question": "ポ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1412eaf5-665a-463a-8975-1eb0ea8f900f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キャット",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "517cd030-0173-4312-85ca-48b174583986"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "パ",
            "rightSide": "pa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ピ",
            "rightSide": "pi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "プ",
            "rightSide": "pu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ペ",
            "rightSide": "pe"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ポ",
            "rightSide": "po"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "パ",
            "rightSide": "pa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ピ",
            "rightSide": "pi"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "プ",
            "rightSide": "pu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ペ",
            "rightSide": "pe"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ポ",
            "rightSide": "po"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2838ee82-dcda-4f72-8f79-31f4afa2e294"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "pa",
            "rightSide": "パ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pi",
            "rightSide": "ピ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pu",
            "rightSide": "プ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pe",
            "rightSide": "ペ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "po",
            "rightSide": "ポ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "pa",
            "rightSide": "パ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pi",
            "rightSide": "ピ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pu",
            "rightSide": "プ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pe",
            "rightSide": "ペ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "po",
            "rightSide": "ポ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "72d2619e-2715-4660-95a4-657e9e1165b1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "パンダ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "パ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ダ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f8e456aa-92c8-4b17-9ea3-b09e0ca9c421"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ポスト",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ポ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8d055a6b-c28d-427e-800d-c5b9eee963df"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ペン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ペ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ff7439f7-ac95-4b61-aeed-d43d1e092bc5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピアノ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ピ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ノ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a320e00e-77ea-48ad-a1c0-c24f62a6196a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "プール",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "プ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ル",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["パ", "ピ", "プ", "ペ", "ポ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "91504798-b576-4724-8db9-9a90b85182f2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "kya",
        "options": ["kya", "kyu", "kyo"],
        "question": "キャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f563ae2e-e921-4a24-97d2-924687f4054d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "kyu",
        "options": ["kya", "kyu", "kyo"],
        "question": "キュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fee70563-6177-4b78-8670-e55cda413b17"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "kyo",
        "options": ["kya", "kyu", "kyo"],
        "question": "キョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fb43362f-ef25-4eb1-8fc2-85bf585c132a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キャ",
        "options": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
        "question": "kya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9bc53b9d-59c1-419a-9bac-55cedfd9d752"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キュ",
        "options": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
        "question": "kyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "546749c6-1137-404d-ab9a-157928a06000"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キョ",
        "options": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
        "question": "kyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2b47dd92-164e-4e27-972a-ad4842c6b492"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キャ",
        "options": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
        "question": "キャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5b0637c0-d63f-4d0f-a57e-f4de16ce47a2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キュ",
        "options": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
        "question": "キュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "11d667c5-9da8-4303-8127-623e3686a29a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キョ",
        "options": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
        "question": "キョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f36db8a9-10b1-4a51-b54c-a028f0769276"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "キャ",
            "rightSide": "kya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "キュ",
            "rightSide": "kyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "キョ",
            "rightSide": "kyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "キャ",
            "rightSide": "kya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "キュ",
            "rightSide": "kyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "キョ",
            "rightSide": "kyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9cf420d3-d76e-46e5-9027-834422515bf2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "kya",
            "rightSide": "キャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "kyu",
            "rightSide": "キュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "kyo",
            "rightSide": "キョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "kya",
            "rightSide": "キャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "kyu",
            "rightSide": "キュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "kyo",
            "rightSide": "キョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fef64d31-d3ae-465a-ad57-1715ebab7c39"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キャベツ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ベ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ツ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "95e21a51-bd6f-4fff-8d42-137f2c9a16d2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キュウリ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["キャ", "キュ", "キョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2bd30846-0c86-4c79-a866-f070f4e08df4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gyu",
        "options": ["gya", "gyu", "gyo"],
        "question": "ギュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4a590331-5905-4538-aaea-02909505472a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "gyo",
        "options": ["gya", "gyu", "gyo"],
        "question": "ギョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0fbd15c6-b56c-4c0c-99bf-0ac8956022e3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギャ",
        "options": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
        "question": "gya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cbdd5027-54cd-4ca4-9317-60f88c411b8d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギュ",
        "options": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
        "question": "gyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9c82a2f1-e2e4-420f-bf0e-dafb56eb83f0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギョ",
        "options": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
        "question": "gyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "46585da2-fd6b-4f1f-9d29-02f0876880c2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギャ",
        "options": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
        "question": "ギャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a34b9bd5-fe92-4064-8b88-c88b07269322"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギュ",
        "options": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
        "question": "ギュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3a88b52f-3e5a-4dbe-bebb-058fe7bd3e2e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギョ",
        "options": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
        "question": "ギョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4d23065d-c354-464e-999e-33df97f1c66d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ギャ",
            "rightSide": "gya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ギュ",
            "rightSide": "gyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ギョ",
            "rightSide": "gyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ギャ",
            "rightSide": "gya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ギュ",
            "rightSide": "gyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ギョ",
            "rightSide": "gyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1933216c-f287-4b42-b621-198bb63133e2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "gya",
            "rightSide": "ギャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gyu",
            "rightSide": "ギュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gyo",
            "rightSide": "ギョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "gya",
            "rightSide": "ギャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gyu",
            "rightSide": "ギュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "gyo",
            "rightSide": "ギョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8a600502-9ef1-478a-8fe6-04cf4b5e5918"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギャクテン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ギ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "テ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "529ec635-35ed-4272-b98d-f2b9a6d45f1b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギュウニュウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ギ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "42db169e-9db4-4d1f-adaa-d7e0738b8f38"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギョウザ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ギ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ザ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a596cd62-c5f7-4562-b2ae-946efc69156f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギャグ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ギ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "グ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "15e5a99f-cc2a-404d-a0c3-3e99cc4b0d4e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ギョク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ギ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2c831b98-f9cd-46ec-9710-3fdbd705ab45"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "sha",
        "options": ["sha", "shu", "sho"],
        "question": "シャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e26e3e3f-5be2-4286-b8f2-6f1e117d0de5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "shu",
        "options": ["sha", "shu", "sho"],
        "question": "シュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b1deb982-d6d9-4454-ae33-77635e537774"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "sho",
        "options": ["sha", "shu", "sho"],
        "question": "ショ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9e818162-f66e-4a10-a378-edc97068099a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シャ",
        "options": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
        "question": "sha"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a3767c21-7f2d-46d8-a101-36c5199b1411"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シュ",
        "options": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
        "question": "shu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "693f38c4-c0e9-49d5-bbd0-ae2582f007e9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ショ",
        "options": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
        "question": "sho"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b18a8d46-ba11-41bc-8cfa-db27ee3a10f1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シャ",
        "options": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
        "question": "シャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9af037eb-5a1e-483d-b6b1-0ddc34c7ae57"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シュ",
        "options": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
        "question": "シュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9a8fc591-f9f2-45a0-90d2-9dd846fb56f8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ショ",
        "options": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
        "question": "ショ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "50002336-4d1c-4371-a8f7-12fb13008d57"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "シャ",
            "rightSide": "sha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "シュ",
            "rightSide": "shu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ショ",
            "rightSide": "sho"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "シャ",
            "rightSide": "sha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "シュ",
            "rightSide": "shu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ショ",
            "rightSide": "sho"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "89fe1c28-3d2c-4520-bf29-cf0fa7913019"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "sha",
            "rightSide": "シャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "shu",
            "rightSide": "シュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "sho",
            "rightSide": "ショ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "sha",
            "rightSide": "シャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "shu",
            "rightSide": "シュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "sho",
            "rightSide": "ショ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "579ec60f-803e-42d9-9ccd-6c60e9d63cf2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シャシン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4f218e3c-aea1-4236-b113-f0833f7d0312"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ショウガ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ガ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "05d439c0-2684-4596-941f-ea353e464c70"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シュミ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "794bddcc-a899-4eb9-bbbf-46cb1b1c16f7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "シャワー",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ワ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "560ef9fd-ad43-4a47-af3e-dda769c5964b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ショクジ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "シ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "849943b5-5e5d-4df9-ac16-6f68c4d1548e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ja",
        "options": ["ja", "ju", "jo"],
        "question": "ジャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "067aa52a-2d9d-4d19-8b8e-97a35bfee195"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ju",
        "options": ["ja", "ju", "jo"],
        "question": "ジュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "857df41c-0425-4f3b-9d00-77e6e97b4aab"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "jo",
        "options": ["ja", "ju", "jo"],
        "question": "ジョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e7c78b82-ab5e-47b3-b9ba-986478661e91"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジャ",
        "options": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
        "question": "ja"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "04633e82-d195-442d-93eb-532d1a3352f7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジュ",
        "options": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
        "question": "ju"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ab93effa-0d59-4ff4-a992-299ab1f7d466"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジョ",
        "options": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
        "question": "jo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8013d6ce-7268-4bd4-89cb-dde43df18ca4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジャ",
        "options": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
        "question": "ジャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "45fd13fb-c6e2-41ce-8567-93207819ae35"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジュ",
        "options": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
        "question": "ジュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "aaa9ecc0-8f2f-475a-b901-b7e9146ff277"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジョ",
        "options": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
        "question": "ジョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5ab265c8-98d3-4a23-8fda-c6cf64002a57"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ジャ",
            "rightSide": "ja"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ジュ",
            "rightSide": "ju"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ジョ",
            "rightSide": "jo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ジャ",
            "rightSide": "ja"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ジュ",
            "rightSide": "ju"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ジョ",
            "rightSide": "jo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0b0bbe81-83a1-4021-bfca-cbf9a08c001c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ja",
            "rightSide": "ジャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ju",
            "rightSide": "ジュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "jo",
            "rightSide": "ジョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ja",
            "rightSide": "ジャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ju",
            "rightSide": "ジュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "jo",
            "rightSide": "ジョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "93077414-2b06-467a-9f02-f17be462f5bb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジョウギ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ギ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7a254ee7-01b2-4669-9069-eafcbe17a912"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジャム",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ム",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a1a010f7-cef3-4ff3-b953-cb150ea6a248"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジュース",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c00201c9-2a00-4854-a248-ab091702ece4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジョギング",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ギ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "グ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0c044562-1c32-4028-bb11-d0c16e43176e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ジャケット",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ケ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "29830adc-a880-4a94-8ee1-7248d066b805"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "cha",
        "options": ["cha", "chu", "cho"],
        "question": "チャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "64e802c0-ecb3-4fee-81ea-c780909a3066"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "chu",
        "options": ["cha", "chu", "cho"],
        "question": "チュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d519138a-e3a7-459d-92c0-7d364ecafadf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "cho",
        "options": ["cha", "chu", "cho"],
        "question": "チョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9c5cd2ae-3bd6-461e-9906-95a53d30c34f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チャ",
        "options": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
        "question": "cha"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "adcedf8f-1cb8-4827-8da0-2c3bb7ec03dd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チュ",
        "options": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
        "question": "chu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2e8224c7-5cdb-4f10-945d-14458dbad92f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チョ",
        "options": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
        "question": "cho"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "78852086-dda3-4f80-bde0-d67c6a17c21d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チャ",
        "options": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
        "question": "チャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "53afa2ae-70e7-44f5-9f9e-3f81a8ad3d30"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チュ",
        "options": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
        "question": "チュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c0a379a8-303a-4c72-a23b-02de5a2c15b2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チョ",
        "options": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
        "question": "チョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "05c07cd5-d52c-491b-9216-984023f643f9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "チャ",
            "rightSide": "cha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "チュ",
            "rightSide": "chu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "チョ",
            "rightSide": "cho"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "チャ",
            "rightSide": "cha"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "チュ",
            "rightSide": "chu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "チョ",
            "rightSide": "cho"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d7c1a628-0819-47bd-b657-c29b3b395605"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "cha",
            "rightSide": "チャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "chu",
            "rightSide": "チュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "cho",
            "rightSide": "チョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "cha",
            "rightSide": "チャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "chu",
            "rightSide": "チュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "cho",
            "rightSide": "チョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "55704ad5-67e9-42de-97b8-bfdb5fb965c6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チョコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ad969843-05e7-4261-afa9-86e25d91bfe6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チャーハン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ハ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "98f7ce98-116c-431a-a6df-0e239a2a1142"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チュウゴク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ゴ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d4719946-d5ca-406d-992b-997c86a6f6c7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チャット",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2afb431a-17d8-4746-a1d4-8ea4693e41a8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チョウチョ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e3a6e004-c9d3-4873-bd68-1f94a0adecaf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "nya",
        "options": ["nya", "nyu", "nyo"],
        "question": "ニャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "697f26a7-5406-4b6c-8c1d-11333bd93968"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "nyu",
        "options": ["nya", "nyu", "nyo"],
        "question": "ニュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d8ec4019-d740-4b8a-8c3f-1e7eea10858c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "nyo",
        "options": ["nya", "nyu", "nyo"],
        "question": "ニョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e2535921-5e12-4b48-a7d5-2a128c23bcff"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニャ",
        "options": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
        "question": "nya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "489d5f16-32d9-4396-bec6-963642ddb3a3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニュ",
        "options": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
        "question": "nyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "26ecc1dd-7a8c-4faa-a69f-59750a7a28e0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニョ",
        "options": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
        "question": "nyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8c2b1429-8aec-4492-8977-811faba1affe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニャ",
        "options": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
        "question": "ニャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "911be049-65b7-4c42-89db-722122fc0728"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニュ",
        "options": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
        "question": "ニュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5341dfec-c495-42be-bfbb-7f650f5ae9af"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニョ",
        "options": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
        "question": "ニョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "766e71a3-c5e1-4f5b-a1fd-3c30718efb71"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ニャ",
            "rightSide": "nya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ニュ",
            "rightSide": "nyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ニョ",
            "rightSide": "nyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ニャ",
            "rightSide": "nya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ニュ",
            "rightSide": "nyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ニョ",
            "rightSide": "nyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8fe6a005-5642-4f5b-a55c-dd4ccae550db"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "nya",
            "rightSide": "ニャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nyu",
            "rightSide": "ニュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nyo",
            "rightSide": "ニョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "nya",
            "rightSide": "ニャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nyu",
            "rightSide": "ニュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "nyo",
            "rightSide": "ニョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "84fede12-fc68-4f43-90d8-00bd4eb82a6b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニューヨーク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ヨ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "32aeec84-0d50-4cb4-8e6d-206bd20d252c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニュース",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "687b0fc9-27cb-4db0-b1bb-5c9da28812f4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニャンコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "804b20fa-76d8-4379-b43a-09e1c52c46d4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニュウイン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9aad5243-0292-4578-8b8b-917b27c6d75a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ニョロニョロ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ロ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ロ",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d5792243-ca5f-45b7-9465-b662164aa4ea"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "hya",
        "options": ["hya", "hyu", "hyo"],
        "question": "ヒャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1322a92c-79f3-490f-9465-b8582bb64b76"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "hyu",
        "options": ["hya", "hyu", "hyo"],
        "question": "ヒュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7870913b-9234-4d7c-996e-b067a1b0fd41"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "hyo",
        "options": ["hya", "hyu", "hyo"],
        "question": "ヒョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "39f232d4-57ee-4009-a6b0-18d44ff2b9c3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒャ",
        "options": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
        "question": "hya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "556acf5f-5b6e-4173-9c31-beea62453023"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒュ",
        "options": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
        "question": "hyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "24afe643-ea57-4cdf-a7c7-b0da95dee708"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒョ",
        "options": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
        "question": "hyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bebbf0e6-3027-4cff-bf7f-e053fe2eda44"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒャ",
        "options": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
        "question": "ヒャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "64e66095-7157-49c3-a396-f81f736558bc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒュ",
        "options": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
        "question": "ヒュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7365144c-531c-4416-a975-c15e031b7a10"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒョ",
        "options": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
        "question": "ヒョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "af6f49c9-f85f-479c-952a-21693113b81d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ヒャ",
            "rightSide": "hya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヒュ",
            "rightSide": "hyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヒョ",
            "rightSide": "hyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ヒャ",
            "rightSide": "hya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヒュ",
            "rightSide": "hyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ヒョ",
            "rightSide": "hyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6c52ed0e-62cc-4419-9bff-8a16cdee5715"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "hya",
            "rightSide": "ヒャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hyu",
            "rightSide": "ヒュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hyo",
            "rightSide": "ヒョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "hya",
            "rightSide": "ヒャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hyu",
            "rightSide": "ヒュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "hyo",
            "rightSide": "ヒョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "87c1058d-ad15-482e-b4f1-f94e22dd4add"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒャクエン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヒ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c1375cf3-4894-49ff-a058-670e7a3933cb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒューマン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヒ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "マ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d2e944dd-f518-4285-9a93-ec51c59087e6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒョウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヒ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4626e1d1-b388-4f0b-89e0-ba52839fae1f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒュウガ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヒ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ガ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6374b431-df2b-4612-b365-2e0640ceac2e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒョウホン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヒ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ホ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c9e1e10c-7837-49bd-ad21-8fb88761ed0a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "bya",
        "options": ["bya", "byu", "byo"],
        "question": "ビャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8a2849cc-d00d-4fda-842f-194cd4ccc8cf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "byu",
        "options": ["bya", "byu", "byo"],
        "question": "ビュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "16772d4c-0eba-4d9d-bb93-5c23437cc11c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "byo",
        "options": ["bya", "byu", "byo"],
        "question": "ビョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "db574dcd-e256-4f7a-8be2-3c3668d386f6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビャ",
        "options": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
        "question": "bya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8cf18224-6c2c-4a10-bd44-17aad48e39c2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビュ",
        "options": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
        "question": "byu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "77031923-8a1f-44d6-a155-1a83651ca9fe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビョ",
        "options": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
        "question": "byo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "908571ca-6481-45eb-a327-e638da95fa93"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビャ",
        "options": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
        "question": "ビャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cb7ac9a7-aa55-46b9-9345-21e954a1dd09"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビュ",
        "options": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
        "question": "ビュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4f435326-ebf3-48bb-8ed5-ed673e3d6381"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビョ",
        "options": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
        "question": "ビョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e56c86e1-2950-4412-a976-77302ee5a5d5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ビャ",
            "rightSide": "bya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ビュ",
            "rightSide": "byu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ビョ",
            "rightSide": "byo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ビャ",
            "rightSide": "bya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ビュ",
            "rightSide": "byu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ビョ",
            "rightSide": "byo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9aaeeb3f-9936-4ef6-870d-8f0844d49cda"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "bya",
            "rightSide": "ビャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "byu",
            "rightSide": "ビュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "byo",
            "rightSide": "ビョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "bya",
            "rightSide": "ビャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "byu",
            "rightSide": "ビュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "byo",
            "rightSide": "ビョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f5a8818c-7472-4587-9b90-0c9754b20bdc"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビューティー",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ビ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "テ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ィ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6c34d6ba-518e-4304-bf49-381264cf1762"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビョウイン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ビ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "43a17a9c-d895-49ba-a7f8-dcaa5c1013e0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビョウキ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ビ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cb6159e2-2c24-4526-9920-15e2581fa5d6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビャクダン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ビ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ダ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a6cdaa50-49c4-4140-a721-29d968d0ef1d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ビュッフェ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ビ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "フ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ェ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d0c0e639-0b7e-4771-882a-f43abcb8abc4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pya",
        "options": ["pya", "pyu", "pyo"],
        "question": "ピャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1c6eb845-23f4-4a97-a4c1-55760db77541"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pyu",
        "options": ["pya", "pyu", "pyo"],
        "question": "ピュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "350bbf91-20a0-4353-b3c0-6fd8a1ef5eab"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pyo",
        "options": ["pya", "pyu", "pyo"],
        "question": "ピョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1b2f88f4-5304-48eb-8f05-9195bda9262d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピャ",
        "options": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
        "question": "pya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1c6a6a51-7a6e-432a-9bf1-06f414024bdb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピュ",
        "options": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
        "question": "pyu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a972af78-0962-4899-8ba6-2105064bf0d6"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピョ",
        "options": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
        "question": "pyo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "77c89721-aaca-4c1c-9d9f-dab23605112f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピャ",
        "options": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
        "question": "ピャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a97463be-d301-446d-aa91-0b737132a678"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピュ",
        "options": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
        "question": "ピュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "507c780b-61d9-4e42-857c-13a0efa99ac3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピョ",
        "options": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
        "question": "ピョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f3b93349-8d87-40d6-9e92-327a68273800"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ピャ",
            "rightSide": "pya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ピュ",
            "rightSide": "pyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ピョ",
            "rightSide": "pyo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ピャ",
            "rightSide": "pya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ピュ",
            "rightSide": "pyu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ピョ",
            "rightSide": "pyo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c842e724-ee52-4810-aed7-a2826ca35eba"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "pya",
            "rightSide": "ピャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pyu",
            "rightSide": "ピュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pyo",
            "rightSide": "ピョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "pya",
            "rightSide": "ピャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pyu",
            "rightSide": "ピュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pyo",
            "rightSide": "ピョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8bb80a28-30e6-4bd5-958f-eea5dae69038"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピアノピョン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ピ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ノ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ピ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cf2060a9-c507-4ee7-8ceb-80ebee7d80ed"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピョウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ピ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "adc34367-7196-4a34-ac7e-7dce52f2f2d4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピュア",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ピ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6e1c8be9-4512-4731-a3ca-2aa3c05e916f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピューマ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ピ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "マ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5a341089-3fc9-4097-ae4c-2888c4530edb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ピャク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ピ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "6cff0753-5096-41e0-9752-fedf64de2e72"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "mya",
        "options": ["mya", "myu", "myo"],
        "question": "ミャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e8c3112c-4d18-4ecf-8d37-2fdf7b76e82d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "myu",
        "options": ["mya", "myu", "myo"],
        "question": "ミュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "506890e3-f44e-49f0-a473-bfa6f9c9e06e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "myo",
        "options": ["mya", "myu", "myo"],
        "question": "ミョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8efe2452-5a3f-4952-98e1-c0457b5ebc6c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミャ",
        "options": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
        "question": "mya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "70c4439d-b351-4493-9c92-4df2ba9bfe04"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミュ",
        "options": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
        "question": "myu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "28620281-f583-424e-b628-cd6136e5b561"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミョ",
        "options": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
        "question": "myo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "067faff4-8960-4f7c-a4f8-44fd996317e1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミャ",
        "options": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
        "question": "ミャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "54ff93f2-5fc6-47e3-847e-fdaf39312d87"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミュ",
        "options": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
        "question": "ミュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e89b0d53-f9b2-4373-b9cf-ec773bbbfb97"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミョ",
        "options": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
        "question": "ミョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d775b070-4257-4e94-a1a4-0b8802e3395b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ミャ",
            "rightSide": "mya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ミュ",
            "rightSide": "myu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ミョ",
            "rightSide": "myo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ミャ",
            "rightSide": "mya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ミュ",
            "rightSide": "myu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ミョ",
            "rightSide": "myo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4751ffd9-e171-4632-9d34-fe15b9f0c936"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "mya",
            "rightSide": "ミャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "myu",
            "rightSide": "ミュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "myo",
            "rightSide": "ミョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "mya",
            "rightSide": "ミャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "myu",
            "rightSide": "ミュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "myo",
            "rightSide": "ミョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7ed76694-b270-401c-ac57-77e8faa38132"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミュージアム",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ム",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e49ee0fb-b962-4ef5-9353-6315c59528ef"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミュージック",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "25e1ecf5-8ef9-4d80-bcc3-86b801f94452"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "コミュニティ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "テ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ィ",
            "number": 5
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4a746cd8-6897-4fda-8b0a-34026ab85408"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アニメミュージック",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ニ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "メ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 4
          },
          {
            "value": "ー",
            "number": 5
          },
          {
            "value": "ジ",
            "number": 6
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 7
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 8
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bdfe536d-20e0-46a4-a694-a073032f3c04"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ミャク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ミ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "eb1a1c57-b602-4cc2-9cb9-8cfd848b2692"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "rya",
        "options": ["rya", "ryu", "ryo"],
        "question": "リャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c2e7c380-392a-49c4-938b-88c438119eab"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ryu",
        "options": ["rya", "ryu", "ryo"],
        "question": "リュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "df534da4-5a79-4a69-9c91-a1289cb9a054"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ryo",
        "options": ["rya", "ryu", "ryo"],
        "question": "リョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cdba263b-84df-4589-8c54-b87c13e69292"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リャ",
        "options": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
        "question": "rya"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "29a6b40d-fda9-47af-98b7-dd2ff42c04dd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リュ",
        "options": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
        "question": "ryu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "15a16107-ab61-4113-a74e-d04151606f4e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リョ",
        "options": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
        "question": "ryo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "3815a198-1e44-4b8c-9f8d-80d4b74ca478"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リャ",
        "options": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
        "question": "リャ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "37be2fbe-c48f-46b4-a5a7-20f338c522c5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リュ",
        "options": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
        "question": "リュ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ca5abe2f-b847-4bfe-a32b-bc5ceeac4a37"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リョ",
        "options": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
        "question": "リョ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4a4467dc-1931-4898-bdd3-26cfb08ec5e9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "リャ",
            "rightSide": "rya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "リュ",
            "rightSide": "ryu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "リョ",
            "rightSide": "ryo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "リャ",
            "rightSide": "rya"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "リュ",
            "rightSide": "ryu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "リョ",
            "rightSide": "ryo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "40a63db8-0462-4c7b-ba2a-9ad5c46a5de4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "rya",
            "rightSide": "リャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ryu",
            "rightSide": "リュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ryo",
            "rightSide": "リョ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "rya",
            "rightSide": "リャ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ryu",
            "rightSide": "リュ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ryo",
            "rightSide": "リョ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bce328be-ba5c-4ecd-ba5a-f12925665384"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リュウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ac41823e-d236-4bcb-9241-68487f3f49c3"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リョクチャ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "57508dd7-bc07-4b04-a2da-a3e0940fa1f0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リャクゴ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ャ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ゴ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c20c63fe-2882-4055-a17a-c96c107bd0a2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リュック",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ュ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fb75b962-6343-40a3-8542-1af1d8768baf"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "リョウリ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "リ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a57381bf-8f9e-48e2-a6f3-e88f01b9af93"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "kk",
        "options": ["kk", "ss", "tt", "pp"],
        "question": "ッ+k"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "03bb30ac-910f-4414-873e-b5bd77d1d1d8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ss",
        "options": ["kk", "ss", "tt", "pp"],
        "question": "ッ+s"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b791466d-4498-4fe9-9921-d52f6aab3939"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "tt",
        "options": ["kk", "ss", "tt", "pp"],
        "question": "ッ+t"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "04c82705-50ae-46ab-9f8f-9b90a6f38586"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "pp",
        "options": ["kk", "ss", "tt", "pp"],
        "question": "ッ+p"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ba058f27-e394-4245-a758-4375118e0b23"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ッ+k",
        "options": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
        "question": "kk"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1090dddb-a281-4b17-8a79-e048f7f2557f"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ッ+s",
        "options": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
        "question": "ss"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fd958167-5bdc-4d8b-8224-6ed62f871280"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ッ+t",
        "options": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
        "question": "tt"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "373ce089-2b96-46fa-9549-36e883afb16a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ッ+p",
        "options": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
        "question": "pp"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ea7664cd-fbff-47a0-97c6-11e15a453abe"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ッ+k",
        "options": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
        "question": "ッ+k"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "5e2038e0-449f-4e9f-8eeb-0f1f67c055df"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ッ+s",
        "options": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
        "question": "ッ+s"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "616dd0da-7ee6-42fc-8dc4-2e160fcc6a8e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ッ+t",
        "options": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
        "question": "ッ+t"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "452b1afb-0c06-423b-9871-aed87eca8c56"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ッ+p",
        "options": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
        "question": "ッ+p"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e731cb90-75f7-455e-9c94-ea2677dcb717"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ッ+k",
            "rightSide": "kk"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ッ+s",
            "rightSide": "ss"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ッ+t",
            "rightSide": "tt"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ッ+p",
            "rightSide": "pp"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ッ+k",
            "rightSide": "kk"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ッ+s",
            "rightSide": "ss"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ッ+t",
            "rightSide": "tt"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ッ+p",
            "rightSide": "pp"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c0b1182d-d2f3-4de7-8117-dfbac706fb63"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "kk",
            "rightSide": "ッ+k"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ss",
            "rightSide": "ッ+s"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "tt",
            "rightSide": "ッ+t"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pp",
            "rightSide": "ッ+p"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "kk",
            "rightSide": "ッ+k"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ss",
            "rightSide": "ッ+s"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "tt",
            "rightSide": "ッ+t"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "pp",
            "rightSide": "ッ+p"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "2b68676c-943b-43ca-b2b0-0cabed234656"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "サッカ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "サ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "777c248c-5016-4915-a588-415474381288"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "カップ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "プ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "dc1d4878-643f-4845-b1c6-415b36fba1a0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "チケット",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "チ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ケ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f8f22463-523e-415d-a7a5-1add60b9b1eb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "テスト",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "テ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0c01fed6-b83e-4be3-b7e6-6b0508484302"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "マップ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "マ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "プ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "57ae886e-fe43-44d0-bd1a-55cfa3f04021"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ヒット",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ヒ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c7803010-0eb7-45d8-9e31-7068677e39d2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "バット",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "バ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4528a7f1-96ea-43b1-ae15-668ab56804f1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ストップ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "プ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a45aa517-5a1a-4798-802c-15896f521a59"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キック",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4e5d760e-ec17-4942-b250-0d2c0849a8e9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "パック",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "パ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ッ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["ッ+k", "ッ+s", "ッ+t", "ッ+p"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "0f7bda61-42c2-4ed4-a24c-0ddb03663801"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "aa",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "アア"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b4319c58-d22b-4392-b9a8-d2e1f73e70d1"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ii",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "イイ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "bfc9384c-68f6-4ee1-8129-0cf4401e8d72"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "uu",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "ウウ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "eb6e0f71-0888-4610-8d5f-7f7e6f6c027c"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ee",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "エエ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7b91c394-f62c-48f1-beac-2019ac31da8b"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "oo",
        "options": ["aa", "ii", "uu", "ee", "oo"],
        "question": "オオ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "cdf35512-25fa-421a-9ef4-3f737b8b5ed7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アア",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "aa"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "752cab62-f61f-4345-b2ab-9425671b0002"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "イイ",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "ii"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "86006d0b-a9f9-4d67-86a7-96b0edaf9e9e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ウウ",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "uu"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "fdcd8435-8107-4f7d-80ce-dc33a55d65e9"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エエ",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "ee"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "69024fad-4212-42c7-999a-ec24caa68802"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オオ",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "oo"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1b76bdc3-6520-45c4-af7e-e91f5b794737"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アア",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "アア"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "386f0c4c-fe11-439c-bb64-8d389564a371"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "イイ",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "イイ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "964cd375-c183-4508-9ce4-77e156b798f8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ウウ",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "ウウ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "00f2e440-affe-4f1a-a97e-164fefdb7687"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エエ",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "エエ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d10f1b0b-84a9-4388-adac-5d4dfc890340"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オオ",
        "options": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
        "question": "オオ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c33a717f-13c9-40c0-8bb0-3272e176a079"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "アア",
            "rightSide": "aa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "イイ",
            "rightSide": "ii"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ウウ",
            "rightSide": "uu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "エエ",
            "rightSide": "ee"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "オオ",
            "rightSide": "oo"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "アア",
            "rightSide": "aa"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "イイ",
            "rightSide": "ii"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ウウ",
            "rightSide": "uu"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "エエ",
            "rightSide": "ee"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "オオ",
            "rightSide": "oo"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "eb938c77-09ed-4916-b5f9-1db895176cf0"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "aa",
            "rightSide": "アア"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ii",
            "rightSide": "イイ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "uu",
            "rightSide": "ウウ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ee",
            "rightSide": "エエ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "oo",
            "rightSide": "オオ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "aa",
            "rightSide": "アア"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ii",
            "rightSide": "イイ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "uu",
            "rightSide": "ウウ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ee",
            "rightSide": "エエ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "oo",
            "rightSide": "オオ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "4072b72a-0374-41d7-8c02-d5160e2435c5"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "コアア",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ceb5d555-cca9-4bac-8541-7c946ff70c84"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アイイ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d88e51a1-9bb7-4968-ad76-dae04d0cda3a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "スウウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ス",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "e0f3168d-f564-473c-9c0e-6ae1a3cabf68"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "セエエ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "セ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c7c5207d-651b-46cb-9f44-7a748c0532df"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オオオ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "オ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "db8e35f3-1ae7-441c-9152-83035b8724c7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ノウウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ノ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ab3dd375-dece-4578-82b4-cce220a4d50a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "アアア",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ア",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f37dc756-2e80-461b-98df-25ba594f672a"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "キイイ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "27c2ba8f-99ed-4acd-8cb5-a7ff8ab3a8fd"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ウウウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a5460204-4592-4319-9de7-74648c48a651"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エエエ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 2
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["アア", "イイ", "ウウ", "エエ", "オオ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "028dd904-0364-4b41-b725-5645e244fec8"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ei",
        "options": ["ei", "ou"],
        "question": "エイ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "56a1d5f1-491d-4f84-9525-79f89dd768b2"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ou",
        "options": ["ei", "ou"],
        "question": "オウ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a1a59647-f7ac-4702-88b0-7246efb95ac7"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エイ",
        "options": ["エイ", "オウ"],
        "question": "ei"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "d5951121-ea9d-40b8-a664-c4483f3a8805"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オウ",
        "options": ["エイ", "オウ"],
        "question": "ou"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_SYMBOL",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9eef64e4-5ae8-47d0-ad24-10f344310db4"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エイ",
        "options": ["エイ", "オウ"],
        "question": "エイ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "656cda24-26a5-4eb3-8f9c-5356a15ddf61"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "オウ",
        "options": ["エイ", "オウ"],
        "question": "オウ"
      },
      "type": "GUESS_THE_LETTER_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "9ac84ac0-36f4-4904-a2db-a9a90a76d528"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "エイ",
            "rightSide": "ei"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "オウ",
            "rightSide": "ou"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "エイ",
            "rightSide": "ei"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "オウ",
            "rightSide": "ou"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": true
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "1cf6b733-01b8-46d7-82b4-9d8211ed7b35"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ei",
            "rightSide": "エイ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ou",
            "rightSide": "オウ"
          }
        ],
        "options": [
          {
            "leftSide": "ei",
            "rightSide": "エイ"
          },
          {
            "leftSide": "ou",
            "rightSide": "オウ"
          }
        ],
        "isLeftSymbol": false
      },
      "type": "MATCHING_TEXT_BY_TEXT",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "19532d03-50cb-461f-b9e3-75ed82ee1479"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "メイコウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "メ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "ad369a04-4f78-45a9-9cb2-08644d1f4989"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "セイコウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "セ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "86d47369-197b-4a29-b170-311fd3cf00cb"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "レイゾウコ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "レ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ゾ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "7460875f-5bcf-416e-b1b7-60a997948c60"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "テイエン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "テ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "b8fb129f-6c66-4e84-89c8-ff1acd7322aa"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "セイフク",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "セ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "フ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ク",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "00d0b1ad-9544-4fe5-a4f0-4bbc5ce3d17e"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ホウセキ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ホ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "セ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "キ",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "f5ee1599-bec2-4d75-8050-ca8801e5ad54"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "トウヒョウ",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ト",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ヒ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ョ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "a4fd37a9-0d77-4ad4-90ca-5df5855f102d"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "コウエン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "コ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "ウ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "c0418087-74b6-46cf-bc52-000844f3b309"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "ケイカン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "ケ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 3
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "8f98ec0c-8624-4719-99d4-96675a86aa10"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "data": {
        "answer": "エイガカン",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "エ",
            "number": 0
          },
          {
            "value": "イ",
            "number": 1
          },
          {
            "value": "ガ",
            "number": 2
          },
          {
            "value": "カ",
            "number": 3
          },
          {
            "value": "ン",
            "number": 4
          }
        ]
      },
      "type": "SORT_THE_ITEMS_BY_SOUND",
      "scoope": ["エイ", "オウ"],
      "letterType": "katakana"
    },
    "deleted": false,
    "id": "71c3790e-56f0-4e2e-a4ad-5e4b80881600"
  }
]
